Gully	en	O
cricket	en	O
chal	hi	O
raha	hi	O
hain	hi	O
yaha	hi	O
"	rest	O
(	rest	O
Soniya	rest	B-PERSON
)	rest	O
Gandhi	rest	B-PERSON
"	rest	O

I	en	O
liked	en	O
a	en	O
@YouTube	en	O
video	en	O
https://t.co/DmVqhZbdaI	en	O
Kabhi	hi	O
Palkon	hi	O
Pe	hi	O
Aasoon	hi	O
Hai-	hi	O
Kishore	hi	B-PERSON
Kumar	hi	I-PERSON
-Vocal	en	O
Cover	en	O
By	en	O
Stephen	en	B-PERSON
Qadir	rest	I-PERSON

Ab	hi	O
yeh	hi	O
kon	hi	O
Bol	hi	O
raha	hi	O
hai	hi	O
Aaj	hi	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
pe	hi	O
Aap	hi	O
wale	hi	O
Delhi	rest	B-PLACE
me	hi	O
WiFi	hi	O
ke	hi	O
sath	hi	O
30	rest	O
min	en	O
Weed	en	O
bhi	hi	O
free	en	O
de	hi	O
rahe	hi	O
hai	hi	O
#	rest	O

RT	en	O
@AfsanaMeet	rest	O
:	rest	O
@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#MSGdedicatesAwardToGuruji	en	O
Naanu	rest	O
papa	en	O
yepieee	en	O
.	rest	O
Congratulations	en	O
and	en	O
celebrations	en	O
.	rest	O
https://t.co/Hn3vFWvdrW	en	O

@kapilv20012001	rest	O
@vaidehisachin	hi	O
log	hi	O
baat	hi	O
samjhane	hi	O
ke	hi	O
liye	hi	O
ek	hi	O
sher	hi	O
padhte	hi	O
hai	hi	O
modiji	hi	B-PERSON
puri	hi	O
gazal	hi	O
padh	hi	O
gaye	hi	O
.	rest	O

Will	en	O
Modi	en	B-PERSON
and	en	O
Manohar	hi	B-PERSON
Parrikar	rest	I-PERSON
apologize	en	O
to	en	O
nation	en	O
for	en	O
fake	en	O
Pak	rest	B-PLACE
Boat	rest	O
?	rest	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
Vyapam	rest	O
#BANvsAFG	rest	O
Pakistan	rest	B-PLACE
Verna	rest	O
#	rest	O
Mumbai	rest	B-PLACE

RT	en	O
@rameshchahal	hi	O
:	rest	O
@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#MSG2In505crOn200thDay	en	O
Superb	en	O
.......	rest	O
guru	hi	O
pa	hi	O
....	rest	O

@JoinAAP	rest	O
@prena_	rest	O
baap	hi	O
re	hi	O
baap	hi	O
free	en	O
khor	hi	O
ho	hi	O
saare	hi	O
Ke	hi	O
saare	hi	O
#AAPtards	rest	O
.	rest	O
Mehnat	hi	O
se	hi	O
kuch	hi	O
mat	hi	O
karna	hi	O

@SANDEEPCOL	rest	O
@narendramodi	rest	O
Tune	hi	O
bola	hi	O
to	hi	O
samajh	hi	O
ho	hi	O
gaya	hi	O
sandy	en	O
bhai	hi	O
..	rest	O
Raat	hi	O
bahut	hi	O
go	hi	O
gayee	hi	O
ja	hi	O
so	hi	O
ja	hi	O
..	rest	O
Nahi	hi	O
to	hi	O
bavala-panti	hi	O
karta	hi	O
rahega	hi	O

@coolfunnytshirt	en	O
250	rest	O
k	hi	O
baad	hi	O
audience	en	O
ko	hi	O
bhi	hi	O
ball	hi	O
dikhayi	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
di	hi	O
hogi	hi	O
aymond	en	O
India	rest	B-PLACE
version	en	O
https://t.co/0vOwIqg2NJ	en	O
via	en	O
@sharethis	en	O

RT	en	O
@mailtosamip	en	O
:	rest	O
Not	en	O
sure	en	O
whats	en	O
more	en	O
challenging	en	O
,	rest	O
listening	en	O
Sonia's	rest	B-PERSON
speech	en	O
or	en	O
hearing	en	O
Tarek	rest	B-PERSON
Shah's	rest	I-PERSON
Angel	en	O
#ScamQueenOnRoad	en	O

@gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#PiousBhandara	rest	O
woww	en	O
great	en	O
papa	en	O
ji	hi	O

Dear	en	O
All	en	O
,	rest	O
Aap	hi	O
sabhi	hi	O
Ko	hi	O
Mahashivratri	rest	O
ki	hi	O
hardik	hi	O
shubhkaamnaye	hi	O
.	rest	O
Thanks	en	O
Vikas	rest	B-PERSON
Kumar-President	en	O
Helpline	en	O
917838021969	rest	O

@SRKsCombatant	en	O
@Imab1d	rest	O
@Pyaari_RiTu__	rest	O
@SrkSaroz	en	O
@SRKsWarrior2_	en	O
acha	hi	O
...	rest	O
kahan	hi	O
chaligeyi	hi	O
he	hi	O
fir	hi	O
wo	hi	O
?	rest	O

@ArvindKejriwal	en	O
Totaly	en	O
chutiyapa	en	O
suru	en	O
kar	hi	O
diya	hi	O
.	rest	O
Yadi	hi	O
tu	hi	O
sahi	hi	O
hai	hi	O
public	en	O
waise	hi	O
hi	hi	O
jita	hi	O
degi	hi	O
.	rest	O
Ye	hi	O
sab	hi	O
nutanki	hi	O
mat	hi	O
kar	hi	O

@meet1973vibe	en	O
Itna	hi	O
sab	hi	O
post	en	O
kiya	hi	O
aur	hi	O
aapko	hi	O
sirf	hi	O
Dimaag	hi	O
hi	hi	O
chahiye	hi	O
:D	rest	O

RT	en	O
@Kailashkher	hi	O
:	rest	O
To	en	O
all	en	O
Kashir	hi	O
Panun	rest	O
Herath	en	O
Mubarak	rest	O
.	rest	O
Happy	en	O
Mahashivratri	en	O
to	en	O
All	en	O
.	rest	O
Shiv	hi	B-PERSON
Shashwat	hi	O
Hain	hi	O
,	rest	O
Sthir	en	O
Hain	hi	O
,	rest	O
ShantSalone	hi	O
Hai	hi	O
,	rest	O
Utpatti	en	O
Ke	hi	O

Tu	hi	O
ho	hi	O
gyi	hi	O
permanent	en	O
kisi	hi	O
or	hi	O
ki	hi	O
,	rest	O
Tujhe	hi	O
chahne	hi	O
wale	hi	O
abi	hi	O
contractual	en	O
hai	hi	O
....	rest	O
Purely	en	O
contractual	en	O
...	rest	O

Audi	hi	B-ORGANISATION
A6	rest	O
for	en	O
Rs	en	O
17	en	O
lakh	hi	O
:	rest	O
Chennai	hi	B-PLACE
after	en	O
flood	en	O
is	en	O
car	en	O
lovers	en	O
paradise	en	O
https://t.co/6SMWlV8Zr0	en	O
"	rest	O
RCC	rest	B-PLACE
road	en	I-PLACE
"	rest	O
(	rest	O
Ghatlodia	rest	B-PLACE
)	rest	O
,	rest	O
its	en	O
a	en	O
line	en	O
of	en	O
Growth	en	O
!!	rest	O

@ashutosh83B	rest	O
Aap	hi	O
jaisa	hi	O
talentd	hi	O
banda	hi	O
jiske	hi	O
pass	hi	O
hoga	hi	O
woh	hi	O
top	en	O
50	rest	O
kya	hi	O
top	en	O
5	rest	O
pe	hi	O
pahunch	hi	O
jayega	hi	O
.	rest	O
Aap	hi	O
AK	hi	B-PERSON
ko	hi	O
Punjab	rest	B-PLACE
bhejke	hi	O
khud	hi	O
Delhi	rest	B-PLACE
ke	hi	O
CM	rest	O
banjao	rest	O
.	rest	O

Dear	en	O
India	rest	B-PLACE
,	rest	O
Ek	hi	O
baar	hi	O
phir	hi	O
bol	hi	O
do	hi	O
"	rest	O
Aany	en	O
dyy	en	O
"	rest	O
#IndvsPak	rest	O
#CWC15	rest	O

RT	en	O
@DainikBhaskar	hi	O
:	rest	O
Aapki	hi	O
Acchi	hi	O
zidd	hi	O
kya	hi	O
hai	hi	O
?	rest	O
https://t.co/8JNuWXcHwg	en	O

RT	en	O
@MukulKMishra	en	O
:	rest	O
Tumhi	hi	O
log	hi	O
bole	hi	O
ki	hi	O
campus	en	O
se	hi	O
police	en	O
hata	hi	O
lo	hi	O
https://t.co/LEziPujl17	en	O

Hindu	rest	O
kaam	hi	O
km	hi	O
krte	hi	O
h	hi	O
or	hi	O
dhapli	hi	O
jyada	hi	O
bjate	hi	O
h	hi	O
...	rest	O
baaki	hi	O
log	hi	O
shanti	hi	O
se	hi	O
apna	hi	O
kaam	hi	O
kr	hi	O
jate	hi	O
h	hi	O
#Gharwapsi	hi	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
@RSS4India	rest	O

RT	en	O
@bdnews_org	en	O
:	rest	O
#bdnews	rest	O
#bangladesh	rest	O
Eight	en	O
militants	en	O
from	en	O
Bangladesh	rest	B-PLACE
surrender	en	O
in	en	O
Tripura	en	B-PLACE
-	rest	O
Business	en	B-ORGANISATION
Standard	rest	I-ORGANISATION
:	rest	O
NewsxEight	en	O
milit	en	O
...	rest	O
https://t	en	O

PIB_India	rest	B-ORGANISATION
#UHF	rest	O
RT	en	O
@MIB_India	rest	O
:	rest	O
#RailBudget2015	rest	O
-	rest	O
Glossary	en	O
of	en	O
Budgetary	en	O
Terms	en	O
(	rest	O
5/5	rest	O
)	rest	O
#	rest	O
RailMinIndia	rest	B-ORGANISATION
http://t.co/2o0ljvHbNN	rest	O

RT	en	O
@ShankarNaresh1	rest	O
:	rest	O
Wish	en	O
U	en	O
Happy	en	O
Mahashivrathiri	en	O
To	en	O
All	en	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
@AnjanaVJ	rest	O
@Manivj07	rest	O
@jan_iyer	rest	O
@iamlakshmirai	rest	O
sunday	en	O
http://t.co/qPzDRUxiOa	en	O

:	rest	O
LAST	en	O
NIGHT	en	O
MAHASHIVRATRI	rest	O
RUDRABHISHEK	rest	O
.....	rest	O
Vastraadi	rest	O
Arpan	hi	O
...	rest	O
http://t.co/bscng4oXJ7	en	O

#RailBudget2015	en	O
higher	en	O
expectations	en	O
...	rest	O
Dikaho	hi	O
ache	hi	O
din	hi	O
...	rest	O
http://t.co/gBjdED9iM5	rest	O

RT	en	O
@makeinindia	rest	O
:	rest	O
India	rest	B-PLACE
has	en	O
recently	en	O
allowed	en	O
up	en	O
to	hi	O
100%	rest	O
#FDI	rest	O
via	en	O
the	en	O
automatic	en	O
route	en	O
for	en	O
medical	en	O
devices	en	O
.	rest	O
#pharmaceuticals	en	O
#MakeInIndia	rest	O
http	en	O

Ramdev	rest	B-PERSON
Baba's	rest	I-PERSON
Train	en	O
-	rest	O
"	rest	O
Yoga	en	O
se	hi	O
Hoga	hi	O
"	rest	O
Express	en	O
#CelebTrains	en	O
#RailBudget2015	en	O
#PrabhuKiRail	rest	O

@NautankiNinja	rest	O
padhaai	hi	O
hi	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
ho	hi	O
paati	hi	O
exam	en	O
ke	hi	O
time	en	O
,	rest	O
major	en	O
reason	en	O
twitter	en	B-ORGANISATION
nkajshuklabjp	rest	O
@bhattkaran83	rest	O
@iambmane	rest	O
@NayakDeep	rest	O
@hbparmar211	rest	O
htt	en	O

PIB_India	rest	B-ORGANISATION
#UHF	rest	O
RT	en	O
MIB_India	rest	B-ORGANISATION
:	rest	O
LIVE	en	O
shortly	en	O
:	rest	O
RailMinIndia	rest	B-ORGANISATION
Minister	en	O
Shri	hi	O
sureshpprabhu	rest	B-PERSON
presenting	en	O
#RailBudget2015	en	O
at	en	O
https://t.co/vGJq4YCXyc	en	O

Behenchod	en	O
twitter	en	B-ORGANISATION
celeb	en	O
.	rest	O
Shikar	hi	B-PERSON
dhawan	hi	I-PERSON
ko	hi	O
replace	en	O
karna	hi	O
chahte	hi	O
the	hi	O
na	hi	O
.	rest	O
#IndvsPak	rest	O

@ImtiyazAzhar	hi	O
Kashmiri	hi	O
citizens	en	O
are	en	O
misled	en	O
by	en	O
the	en	O
propaganda	en	O
spread	en	O
by	en	O
the	en	O
anti-India	en	O
forces	en	O
in	en	O
and	en	O
outside	en	O
Kashmir	hi	B-PLACE

@narendramodi	rest	O
ji	hi	O
,	rest	O
will	en	O
come	en	O
to	hi	O
India	rest	B-PLACE
directly	en	O
with	en	O
French	en	O
president	en	O
on	en	O
Republic	en	O
day	en	O

Sonakshi	rest	B-PERSON
Sinha	rest	I-PERSON
out	en	O
of	en	O
the	en	O
Hasina	hi	O
Biopic	en	O
!	rest	O
https://t.co/hID75opFyz	en	O

@NeelakshiGswm	en	O
@narendramodi	rest	O
@ArvindKejriwal	en	O
he	en	O
doesnot	en	O
need	en	O
to	hi	O
do	hi	O
anything	en	O
miss	en	O
,	rest	O
jst	en	O
haryana	hi	B-PLACE
se	hi	O
water	en	O
block	en	O
karwa	hi	O
do	hi	O
,	rest	O
ek	hi	O
mahine	hi	O
me	hi	O
ro	hi	O
denge	hi	O

PM	rest	O
Modi's	rest	B-PERSON
contribution	en	O
in	en	O
international	en	O
arena	en	O
is	en	O
remarkable	en	O
:	rest	O
Sri	hi	B-PERSON
Sri	hi	B-PERSON
Ravi	rest	I-PERSON
Shankar	rest	I-PERSON
https://t.co/gjwxKvu3dY	en	O

RT	en	O
@DarrKeAage	en	O
:	rest	O
Main	hi	O
banunga	hi	O
ji	hi	O
Goodwill	en	O
Ambassador	hi	O
.	rest	O
https://t.co/A7iQdAqrxY	en	O

@reddyvpr	en	O
CORRECT	en	O
...	rest	O
Well	en	O
said	en	O
..	rest	O
REMOVE	en	O
SUBSIDIARIES	en	O
before	en	O
you	en	O
harp	en	O
on	en	O
SUBSIDIES	en	O
..	rest	O
#SuperBudget	en	O
#TamilNadu	rest	O
#AIADMK	rest	O
#AyuthaEzhuthu	hi	O

MerryXmas	en	O
From	en	O
TeamShivaay	en	O
bas	hi	O
diwali	hi	O
2016	rest	O
ka	hi	O
wait	en	O
hai	hi	O

@TandonRaveena	rest	O
@BeingSalmanKhan	rest	O
tumse	hi	O
jo	hi	O
dekhte	hi	O
hi	hi	O
.	rest	O
...	rest	O
kabhi	hi	O
charniroad	hi	O
,	rest	O
kabhi	hi	O
...	rest	O
was	en	O
lovely	en	O
...	rest	O

#BecauseOfTwitter	en	O
i	en	O
could	en	O
interact	en	O
with	en	O
my	en	O
childhood	en	O
loves	en	O
@iHrithik	en	O
@iamsrk	en	O
and	en	O
my	en	O
jawaani	hi	O
wale	hi	O
loves	en	O
@Varun_dvn	en	O
@aliaa08	rest	O

Beta	hi	O
aapse	hi	O
na	hi	O
ho	hi	O
paega	hi	O
!	rest	O
patake	hi	O
OLX	rest	B-ORGANISATION
pe	hi	O
bech	hi	O
do	hi	O
!!!!	rest	O
#IndVsPak	rest	O

RT	en	O
AAP_Najafgarh	hi	B-ORGANISATION
"	rest	O
RT	en	O
NavbharatTimes	en	B-ORGANISATION
:	rest	O
neeerajbadhwar	hi	O
,	rest	O
...	rest	O
#Vi	rest	O
https://t.co/0Nz3pd4cV3	en	O
"	rest	O

Cordial	en	O
Invitation	en	O
:	rest	O
Mahashivratri	rest	O
Utsav	en	O
@	rest	O
Shrutisagar	hi	B-PLACE
Ashram	en	I-PLACE
17	en	O
Feb	en	O
8am	rest	O
-18	rest	O
Feb	en	O
1am	en	O
#ShrutisagarAshram	en	O
#NonDualism	rest	O
#Mahashivratri	rest	O

@aamir_khan	hi	O
Mauke	hi	O
pr	hi	O
Chauka	hi	O
lga	hi	O
diya	hi	O
..	rest	O
Well	en	O
Played	en	O
:)	rest	O
#MenInBlue	en	O
#MaukaMauka	rest	O
#IndvsSA	rest	O

Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
Unwell	en	O
,	rest	O
Won't	en	O
Visit	en	O
Puducherry	en	B-PLACE
Where	en	O
Death	en	O
Threat	en	O
Was	en	O
Received	en	O
:	rest	O
In	en	O
late	en	O
night	en	O
tweets	en	O
,	rest	O
...	rest	O
https://t.co/nx0U2O5zzB	en	O
via	en	O
@ndtv	en	O

@raonabeel	rest	O
I	en	O
hv	en	O
utmost	en	O
respect	en	O
4	en	O
Imran	en	B-PERSON
Khan	hi	I-PERSON
.	rest	O
But	en	O
not	en	O
for	en	O
Shahid	en	B-PERSON
Afridi	en	I-PERSON
.	rest	O
&	rest	O
even	en	O
Ali	hi	B-PERSON
Zafar	hi	I-PERSON
said	en	O
that	en	O
whole	en	O
Pakistan	rest	B-PLACE
is	en	O
fed	en	O
up	en	O
of	en	O
Afridi	en	B-PERSON
.	rest	O

Sir	hi	O
Jadeja	hi	B-PERSON
ne	hi	O
apni	hi	O
wicket	en	O
Ki	hi	O
compromise	en	O
kar	hi	O
li	hi	O
hai	hi	O
!	rest	O
Sir	hi	O
!	rest	O
Respect	en	O
!	rest	O
#INDvsPAK	rest	O

RT	en	O
@ArvindKejriwal	en	O
:	rest	O
All	en	O
medicines	en	O
are	en	O
now	en	O
available	en	O
free	en	O
in	en	O
Delhi	en	B-PLACE
Govt	en	O
hospitals	en	O
https://t.co/Ux8A3dp4g2	en	O

RT	en	O
AnkitaInsa	rest	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
RT	en	O
jsingh341	en	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
RT	en	O
drajayam_ajay	hi	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
RT	en	O
SuyashInsan	rest	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
Gurmeetramrahim	en	B-PERSON
thank	en	O
u	en	O
pitaji	hi	O
n	en	O
come	en	O
soon	en	O
be	en	O
with	en	O
me	hi	O
always	en	O
#MustWatchMSG	en	O
#	rest	O

RT	en	O
@nitibnsl	en	O
:	rest	O
#DSSFoundationDay	en	O
swarg	en	O
Dharti	hi	O
par	hi	O
dekhna	hi	O
hai	hi	O
to	hi	O
ek	hi	O
visit	en	O
Dera	hi	O
Sacha	hi	O
Sauda	hi	O
at	en	O
Sirsa	en	B-PLACE
ki	hi	O
ho	hi	O
Jaaye	hi	O
https://t.co/e8Tj1HRPjt	en	O

@Ashishtics	en	O
tou	en	O
mein	hi	O
kounsa	hi	O
uspenfilm	en	O
banane	hi	O
wala	hi	O
hu	hi	O
@Obnoxious_Ravan	en	O

Uska	hi	O
dimple	hi	O
Mere	hi	O
header	en	O
ko	hi	O
khoobsurat	hi	O
karaha	hi	O

Param	hi	O
Pujye	hi	O
sant	hi	O
Shiri	hi	B-PERSON
Ashsram	en	I-PERSON
g	en	I-PERSON
bapu	rest	I-PERSON
ke	hi	O
swasthye	hi	O
Yash	hi	O
kirti	hi	O
hetu	rest	O
,	rest	O
mahashivratri	rest	O
ke	hi	O
avsar	hi	O
per	hi	O
Ludhiana	rest	B-PLACE
me	hi	O
.	rest	O
sadhkon	hi	O
http://t.co/Trakdy1njz	en	O

Happy	en	O
#Mahashivratri	rest	O
to	en	O
everyone	en	O
.	rest	O
Jai	hi	O
Mahadev	rest	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Jai	hi	O
Bholeshankar	hi	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Jai	hi	O
ho	hi	O
Mahakaal	hi	B-PERSON
ki	hi	O
.	rest	O

#ZalmiRocks	en	O
yahan	hi	O
ek	hi	O
wicket	en	O
ki	hi	O
zarorat	rest	O
hy	en	O

@justbeauty18	en	O
Abi	hi	O
koi	hi	O
kasaar	hi	O
baqi	hi	O
hy	hi	O
?	rest	O
:D	rest	O

Muharam	rest	O
celebrations	en	O
in	en	O
Indian	rest	O
hyderabad	rest	B-PLACE
#IndvsPak	rest	O
#	rest	O
#IndWins	rest	O
#WorldCup	en	O
#FuckYouPak	rest	O

#IndvsSA	rest	O
I	en	O
have	en	O
told	en	O
today	en	O
morning	en	O
killed	en	O
hum	hi	O
mauke	hi	O
pe	hi	O
chuka	hi	O
marenge	hi	O
......	rest	O

@Obnoxious_Ravan	en	O
Dil	hi	O
tod	hi	O
diya	hi	O
janeman	hi	O
...	rest	O
ab	hi	O
ni	hi	O
aaunga	hi	O
mai	hi	O
wapis	en	O
twitter	en	B-ORGANISATION
pe	hi	O
:\	rest	O
@gillraman705	rest	O
@confusedbf_	rest	O

Na	hi	O
Jane	hi	O
kb	hi	O
Koi	hi	O
Tara	hi	O
Toot	hi	O
Jae	hi	O
;	rest	O
Na	hi	O
Jane	hi	O
Kb	hi	O
Koi	hi	O
Aansu	hi	O
Aankh	hi	O
Se	hi	O
Chhoot	hi	O
Jaye	hi	O
;	rest	O
Kuch	hi	O
Pal	hi	O
Hamare	hi	O
Sath	hi	O
Bhi	hi	O
Has	hi	O
Lo	hi	O
;	rest	O
Na	hi	O
Jane	hi	O
Kb	hi	O
Tumhare	hi	O
Daant	hi	O
Toot	hi	O
Jae	hi	O
!	rest	O

@sachin_rt	en	O
&	rest	O
Suresh	en	B-PERSON
Prabhu	rest	I-PERSON
,	rest	O
railway	en	O
minister	en	O
belong	en	O
to	en	O
same	en	O
school	en	O
,	rest	O
Shardashram	hi	B-ORGANISATION
vidya	hi	I-ORGANISATION
mandir	rest	I-ORGANISATION
...	rest	O
#RailBudget2015	rest	O

@MahnooriAhmed	rest	O
ya	hi	O
alllah	hi	O
yeh	hi	O
kya	hi	O
kiya	hi	O
hahahah	rest	O

RT	en	O
@cricketnext	en	O
:	rest	O
Just	en	O
in	en	O
:	rest	O
Cricketer	en	O
Ravindra	rest	B-PERSON
Jadeja's	rest	I-PERSON
marriage	en	O
runs	en	O
into	en	O
controversy	en	O
after	en	O
gunfire	en	O
shots	en	O
during	en	O
marriage	en	O
procession	en	O

#IndvsPak	rest	O
koi	hi	O
ye	hi	O
to	hi	O
btao	hi	O
ye	hi	O
hmare	hi	O
player	en	O
face	en	O
p	hi	O
kch	hi	O
lga	hi	O
k	hi	O
ae	hi	O
h	hi	O
ya	hi	O
pak	hi	B-PLACE
s	en	O
match	en	O
ki	hi	O
khushi	hi	O
m	hi	O
special	en	O
facial	en	O
?	rest	O
:-P	rest	O

RT	en	O
@INCIndia	rest	O
:	rest	O
Shri	hi	O
Modi	rest	B-PERSON
in	en	O
a	en	O
tweet	en	O
on	en	O
31.3.2014	rest	O
said	en	O
,	rest	O
"	rest	O
Italian	rest	O
marines	en	O
mercilessly	en	O
killed	en	O
our	en	O
fishermen	en	O
.	rest	O
If	en	O
Madam	en	O
is	en	O
so	en	O
'	rest	O
patriotic	en	O
'	rest	O
can	en	O
she	en	O

Feelng	en	O
hawa	hi	O
hawai	hi	O
aftr	en	O
two	en	O
packs	en	O
of	en	O
bhang	rest	O
...	rest	O
har	hi	O
har	hi	O
mahadev	rest	B-PERSON
#mahashivratri	rest	O

@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#MSGmissionHumanity	en	O
Thank	en	O
You	en	O
Guruji	en	O
.	rest	O
Good	en	O
Morning	en	O
&	rest	O
Lov	en	O
You	en	O
.	rest	O
Pita	hi	O
ji	hi	O
bless	en	O
me	hi	O
for	en	O
more	en	O
sewa	en	O
simran	en	O
.	rest	O
https://t.co/EnUVUDW22A	en	O

Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Dravid	en	I-PERSON
You're	en	O
Our	en	O
Lucky	en	O
Charm	rest	O
:')	rest	O
#DDvKKR	rest	O

Can	en	O
We	en	O
Trend	en	O
MAHASHIVRATRI/SHIVRATI	rest	O
KI	hi	O
SHUBHKAMNAYE	hi	O
In	en	O
Hindi	en	O
Tmrw	en	O
?	rest	O
@missionbihar	rest	O
@yesiamsaffron	en	O
@aditispeaks_	en	O
@rss_org	en	O

Swim	en	O
swim	en	O
#giabby	en	O
excited	en	O
@	rest	O
Shangri-La's	rest	B-ORGANISATION
Rasa	hi	B-PLACE
Sentosa	en	I-PLACE
Resort	en	I-PLACE
&	rest	O
Spa	rest	O
https://t.co/bBk1e6H7jP	rest	O

@amitava258	rest	O
I	en	O
think	en	O
Vipul	en	B-PERSON
was	en	O
dropped	en	O
...	rest	O
Aankhen	hi	O
2	rest	O
will	en	O
probably	en	O
be	en	O
directed	en	O
by	en	O
Aneez	en	B-PERSON
Bazmi	hi	I-PERSON

Roger's	en	B-PERSON
potentialpathin	en	O
Madrid	en	B-PLACE
open	en	O
:	rest	O
1R	rest	O
:	rest	O
Bye	en	O
2R	rest	O
:	rest	O
Mahut	rest	B-PERSON
or	hi	O
Sousa	rest	B-PERSON
3R	rest	O
:	rest	O
Thiem	en	B-PERSON
QF	rest	O
:	rest	O
Rafa	rest	B-PERSON
SF	rest	O
:	rest	O
Murray	en	B-PERSON
Final	en	O
:	rest	O
Novak	rest	B-PERSON
#AllezRoger	en	O

RT	en	O
@Babu_Bhaiyaa	rest	O
:	rest	O
This	en	O
outcry	en	O
by	en	O
Sonia	en	B-PERSON
G	en	I-PERSON
is	en	O
her	en	O
way	en	O
of	en	O
saying-Kya	hi	O
Modi	hi	B-PERSON
ji	hi	O
!	rest	O
Hum	hi	O
yahan	hi	O
Opposition	en	O
mai	hi	O
baith	hi	O
kr	hi	O
bhi	hi	O
scam	en	O
kr	hi	O
sakte	hi	O
hain	hi	O
.	rest	O
Tum	hi	O
Gov	en	O

Ghar	hi	O
beth	hi	O
Kay	hi	O
..	rest	O
Ki	hi	O
banay	hi	O
ga	hi	O
es	hi	O
mulak	hi	O
da	hi	O
.	rest	O
#	rest	O
_	rest	O
_	rest	O

Hindustan	rest	B-PLACE
ki	hi	O
aisi	hi	O
takdeer	hi	O
likh	hi	O
maula	hi	O
,	rest	O
Ki	hi	O
log	hi	O
Sanskrit	rest	O
me	hi	O
allah	hi	O
aur	hi	O
Urdu	rest	O
me	hi	O
ram	hi	B-PERSON
likhe	hi	O
....	rest	O

"	rest	O
@sri50	rest	O
:	rest	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
today	en	O
.	rest	O
Hara	hi	O
Hara	hi	O
Mahadev	rest	B-PERSON
.	rest	O
"	rest	O
Ivarkum	en	O
therichirukku	en	O
ha	hi	O
ha	hi	O
..	rest	O
@rj_janakarajan	rest	O
@shyamkkumar	hi	O

"	rest	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
,	rest	O
joke	en	O
to	hi	O
suna	hi	O
hoga	hi	O
?	rest	O
"	rest	O
#TwistedBollywoodDialogues	en	O
#RahulOnLeave	en	O
#WhereIsRahul	en	O

Lag	hi	O
rha	hi	O
hai	hi	O
aaj	hi	O
Rahul	hi	B-PERSON
Gandhi	hi	I-PERSON
Zimbabwe	hi	B-PLACE
ka	hi	O
Support	en	O
kr	hi	O
rhe	hi	O
the	hi	O
.	rest	O
#WhereIsRahulGandhi	rest	O
#WhereIsRahul	rest	O

Are	hi	O
you	en	O
talking	en	O
about	en	O
Sonia	rest	B-PERSON
Gandhi's	rest	I-PERSON
work	en	O
schedule	en	O
in	en	O
the	en	O
future	en	O
??	rest	O
#WomensDay	en	O
https://t.co/G5XnpPtj46	en	O

RT	en	O
@Being_Humor	en	O
:	rest	O
Selfie	en	O
in	en	O
panoramma	en	O
mode	en	O
https://t.co/tdoXQqvhVN	en	O

#	rest	O
_	rest	O
_	rest	O
gandi	rest	O
baat	hi	O
p	hi	O
larkiya	hi	O
block	en	O
kyu	hi	O
marte	hi	O
h	hi	O
?	rest	O

RT	en	O
@Ekta555	rest	O
:	rest	O
@insan_honey	rest	O
#MSGmissionHumanity	en	O
Good	en	O
Night	en	O
Dii	hi	O
ji	hi	O
https://t.co/t2B1es8Q78	en	O
lead	en	O
to	en	O
the	en	O
Lonely	en	O
Pl	rest	O
...	rest	O
https://t.co/RK3yFhYSg4	en	O

@sandhirians	rest	O
@SanDhirHolics	rest	O
@SanDhirParShFC	rest	O
insta	rest	B-ORGANISATION
wala	hi	O
pic	en	O
...	rest	O
other	en	O
grp	en	O
...	rest	O
but	en	O
bada	hi	O
mast	hi	O
hai	hi	O
..	rest	O
http://t.co/o0De8Pmhzl	en	O

It	en	O
runs	en	O
in	en	O
the	en	O
family	en	O
:	rest	O
Mujtaba	rest	B-PERSON
Saail	rest	I-PERSON
and	en	O
Madiha	rest	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
Mujtaba	rest	B-PERSON
Saail	rest	I-PERSON
,	rest	O
owner	en	O
of	en	O
Almas	en	B-ORGANISATION
and	en	O
sibling	en	O
Madiha	rest	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
...	rest	O
https://t.co/kPTckL4wNI	en	O
#etribune	rest	O

Delhi	rest	B-PLACE
to	hi	O
Dholakpur	hi	B-PLACE
(	rest	O
Chhota	hi	B-PERSON
Bheem	hi	I-PERSON
)	rest	O
new	en	O
train	en	O
announce	en	O
na	hi	O
karne	hi	O
ki	hi	O
wajeh	hi	O
se	hi	O
,	rest	O
Congress	en	B-ORGANISATION
ne	hi	O
#RailBudget2015	en	O
ko	hi	O
disappointed	en	O
declare	en	O
kar	hi	O
diya	hi	O
hai	hi	O
.	rest	O

RT	en	O
@ScoopWhoop	en	O
:	rest	O
Dhawan	hi	B-PERSON
be	en	O
like	en	O
...	rest	O
Maika	hi	O
hai	hi	O
mera	hi	O
!	rest	O
http://t.co/Kw1rJGJL4j	rest	O

RT	en	O
ihsavru_	en	O
:	rest	O
pruthapartha	hi	O
UNSFP	rest	O
#Mahashivratri	rest	O
ka	hi	O
#Fever104	en	O
11:00	rest	O
AM	hi	O
ke	hi	O
program	en	O
ka	hi	O
update	en	O
hai	hi	O
kahin	hi	O
?	rest	O

@aajtak	hi	O
Abe	hi	O
Pagalo	hi	O
degree	hi	O
nakli	hi	O
hai	hi	O
,	rest	O
Aajtak	hi	B-ORGANISATION
wale	hi	O
ank	hi	O
gin	hi	O
rahe	hi	O
hai	hi	O
ROFL	en	O

Kalloori	hi	B-PERSON
Vasal	rest	I-PERSON
-	rest	O
Tips/Guidance	en	O
For	en	O
Common	en	O
Law	en	O
Admission	en	O
Test	en	O
(	rest	O
05/05/2015	rest	O
)	rest	O
-	rest	O
Thanthi	hi	B-ORGANISATION
TV	en	I-ORGANISATION
-	rest	O
TamilTwin	en	O
http://t.co/ERNCIdSGZi	en	O

RT	en	O
@asot	en	O
:	rest	O
Bring	en	O
out	en	O
that	en	O
buffalo	en	O
..	rest	O
@TheVoiceOfGaia	en	O
'	rest	O
Inyathi	rest	O
'	rest	O
Taken	en	O
from	en	O
#ASOT2016	rest	O
#ASOT762	rest	O

RT	en	O
@tivra123	rest	O
:	rest	O
,	rest	O
,	rest	O
..	rest	O
!	rest	O
Bharat	hi	B-PLACE
Mata	hi	O
Ki	hi	O
Jai	hi	O
https://t.co/WTm1HoKvBy	en	O

Mujhe	hi	O
gam	hi	O
hai	hi	O
ki	hi	O
mainezindagi	hi	O
me	hi	O
kuch	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
paya	hi	O
Ye	hi	O
gam	hi	O
fil	en	O
se	hi	O
nikal	hi	O
jaye	hi	O
agar	hi	O
tum	hi	O
milne	hi	O
aajao	hi	O
@Rekhta	hi	O

ISRO	en	B-ORGANISATION
should	en	O
think	en	O
about	en	O
replacing	en	O
PSLV	en	O
with	en	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
.	rest	O
He	en	O
can	en	O
also	en	O
be	en	O
re-launched	en	O
7	en	O
to	hi	O
10	rest	O
times	en	O
#RahulRally	en	O
#RahulReturns	en	O
#PappuFarce	en	O

RT	en	O
@dubash	rest	O
:	rest	O
This	en	O
is	en	O
how	en	O
you	en	O
criticize	en	O
the	en	O
Congress	en	B-ORGANISATION
and	en	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
.	rest	O
Learn	en	O
,	rest	O
people	en	O
.	rest	O
https://t.co/T0Kn4W33ja	en	O

AAJ	hi	O
virat	rest	B-PERSON
bc	rest	O
asnushka	hi	B-PERSON
jo	hi	O
pk	hi	O
me	hi	O
pakistani	rest	O
guy	en	O
ko	hi	O
date	en	O
krti	hi	O
h	hi	O
na	hi	O
uska	hi	O
badla	hi	O
le	hi	O
rha	hi	O
h	hi	O
...	rest	O
:D	rest	O
#IndvsPak	rest	O

RT	en	O
@Puja_FC	rest	O
:	rest	O
3	rest	O
parvatis	en	O
of	en	O
mahadev	rest	O
@BanPuja	rest	O
@BSonarika	rest	O
@_suhasidhami	rest	O
wid	en	O
lord	en	O
shiva	rest	B-PERSON
:)	rest	O
hpy	en	O
mahashivratri	rest	O
#parvatians	rest	O
:)	rest	O
@LifeOKTV	en	O
http://t	en	O
.	rest	O

RT	en	O
@shuvankr	en	O
:	rest	O
Karor-pati	hi	O
naam	hi	O
kharid	hi	O
sakenge	hi	O
..	rest	O
Guess	en	O
Shiv	en	B-ORGANISATION
Sena	en	I-ORGANISATION
will	en	O
be	en	O
happy	en	O
if	en	O
CST	en	B-PLACE
is	en	O
renamed	en	O
as	en	O
Chhratrapati	en	B-PLACE
Ambani	rest	I-PLACE
Station	en	I-PLACE
#RailBudget2	en	O

.	rest	O
@AashishKhetan	rest	O
on	en	O
#Periscope	en	O
:	rest	O
PC	rest	O
at	en	O
Chandigarh	hi	B-PLACE
AAP	hi	B-ORGANISATION
expose	en	O
Majithia	rest	B-PERSON
https://t.co/pCRok88MqL	en	O
OnLeave	en	O

#IndvsPak	rest	O
ab	hi	O
Kya	hi	O
hoga	hi	O
tumhaara	hi	O
next	en	O
Diwali	hi	O
maybe	en	O

jis	hi	O
jamhooriyat	hi	O
ko	hi	O
aap	hi	O
bachaane	hi	O
nikli	hi	O
hain	hi	O
,	rest	O
janaab-e-aali	hi	O
uski	hi	O
aap	hi	O
hi	hi	O
ki	hi	O
sarkaar	hi	O
ne	hi	O
bahut	hi	O
pehle	hi	O
dhajjiyaan	hi	O
uda	hi	O
di	hi	O
thi	hi	O
#NotUsingHashtag	hi	O

@Dervishious	en	O
@madihajihan	rest	O
fouj	rest	O
bhe	hi	O
sab	hi	O
dekh	hi	O
he	hi	O
rahee	hi	O
mufahimat	hi	O
walay	hi	O
ab	hi	O
bahut	hi	O
strong	en	O
hain	hi	O
Zardare	hi	O
na	hi	O
mufahimat	hi	O
kara	hi	O
kar	hi	O
fouj	rest	O
ko	hi	O
bhe	hi	O
lagam	hi	O
d	hi	O

@RahulReply	en	O
very	en	O
few	en	O
"	rest	O
acchi	hi	O
ladkiya	hi	O
"	rest	O
left	en	O
...	rest	O
save	en	O
them	en	O

#	rest	O
_	rest	O
_	rest	O
mujhe	hi	O
tumpe	hi	O
dil	hi	O
agya	hi	O
h	hi	O

Perfect	en	O
railway	en	O
budget	en	O
#BudgetBT	en	O
#	rest	O
#RailBudget2015	rest	O
#IndianRailways	rest	O
@abpnewstv	en	O
@aajtakki	hi	O
to	hi	O
jal	hi	O
gyi	hi	O
,	rest	O
pata	hi	O
ni	hi	O
Konya	hi	O
milk	hi	O
h	hi	O
inka	hi	O

RT	en	O
@nooR_inSan	en	O
:	rest	O
@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
hhhuuuurrraayyyyy	en	O
#MSGdedicatesAwardToGuruji	en	O
#MSGdedicatesAwardToAllFans	en	O
thnku	en	O
bapu	rest	O

@BJP_Brigade	rest	O
vote	en	O
for	en	O
a	en	O
safe	en	O
delhi	rest	B-PLACE
#vote	en	O
for	en	O
kiranbedi	hi	B-PERSON
#AbkiBaarBediSarkaar	hi	O
.	rest	O

RT	en	O
@ashutosh83B	rest	O
:	rest	O
Murderous	en	O
assault	en	O
on	en	O
AAP	rest	B-ORGANISATION
MLA	rest	O
,	rest	O
Kartar	hi	B-PERSON
Singh	rest	I-PERSON
Tanwar	rest	I-PERSON
.	rest	O
Chhatarpur	rest	B-PLACE
.	rest	O
Driver	en	O
is	en	O
injured	en	O
.	rest	O
Attackers	en	O
were	en	O
carrying	en	O
pistol	en	O
.	rest	O
Kartar	hi	B-PERSON
i	hi	O

Kuch	hi	O
bevkuf	en	O
log	hi	O
abhi	hi	O
se	hi	O
PM	rest	O
banne	hi	O
ki	hi	O
soch	hi	O
rahe	hi	O
he	hi	O
.	rest	O
Iska	hi	O
@NitishKumar	hi	O
or	hi	O
@ArvindKejriwal	hi	O
se	hi	O
koi	hi	O
sambandh	rest	O
nahi	hi	O
he	hi	O
.	rest	O
#SoniaBribedMedia	rest	O

MahaShivRatri	rest	O
ki	hi	O
hardhik	hi	O
shubhkamnayy	hi	O
...	rest	O
On	en	O
Namah	rest	O
Shivaya	rest	B-PERSON
...	rest	O
God	en	O
Bless	en	O
...	rest	O

Galey	hi	O
me	hi	O
chain	en	O
.	rest	O
Haath	hi	O
me	hi	O
kadaa	hi	O
.	rest	O
Sar	hi	O
k	hi	O
upar	hi	O
topi	hi	O
.	rest	O
Ghutno	hi	O
k	hi	O
upar	hi	O
tak	hi	O
chaddi	hi	O
.	rest	O
Abbey	hi	O
gareebon	hi	O
k	hi	O
50Cent	en	O
gym	en	O
me	hi	O
aaya	hi	O
h	hi	O
ya	hi	O
gaana	hi	O
gaane	hi	O
bc	hi	O

RT	en	O
@ShoaibDaniyal	rest	O
:	rest	O
Gujarat	rest	B-PLACE
infant	en	O
mortality	en	O
is	en	O
3X	rest	O
of	en	O
Kerala	rest	B-PLACE
.	rest	O
For	en	O
every	en	O
one	en	O
lakh	hi	O
births	en	O
,	rest	O
2800	rest	O
more	en	O
Gujju	en	O
babies	en	O
die	en	O
<	rest	O
12	rest	O
m	hi	O
than	en	O
Mallu	en	O
.	rest	O
http	en	O

#MahaShivratri	rest	O
Har	hi	O
Har	hi	O
Mahadev	rest	B-PERSON
!!	rest	O
RT	en	O
@JasumatiPatel	en	O
:	rest	O
I	en	O
love	en	O
shiv	en	B-PERSON
!	rest	O
|	rest	O
Photography	en	O
by	en	O
Jasumati	en	B-PERSON
Patel	en	I-PERSON
http://t.co/5mXJrM5fLW	en	O

Shruti	hi	B-PERSON
Performing	en	O
at	en	O
music	en	O
awards	en	O
Anbe	en	O
Sivam	en	O
Her	en	O
Voice	en	O
_/\_	rest	O
#HappyBirthdayShrutihassan	hi	O
https://t.co/3XHIfCXPmK	en	O
via	en	O
@YouTube	en	O

RT	en	O
@SrBachchan	rest	O
:	rest	O
goodness	rest	O
...	rest	O
!	rest	O
Vishwanath	en	B-PERSON
Gavaskar	en	B-PERSON
Sachin	en	B-PERSON
under	en	O
one	en	O
garland	rest	O
..	rest	O
!!!	rest	O
https://t.co/ZpkJFc4Ouj	rest	O

BJP	rest	B-ORGANISATION
Presents	en	O
Proof	en	O
Of	en	O
PM's	en	O
Degrees	en	O
,	rest	O
Demands	en	O
Apology	en	O
From	en	O
Kejriwal	en	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
Senior	en	O
Bharatiya	hi	B-ORGANISATION
Janata	hi	I-ORGANISATION
Party	en	I-ORGANISATION
(	rest	O
BJP	rest	B-ORGANISATION
)	rest	O
leader	en	O
...	rest	O
https://t.co/jcayIlmZZG	en	O

RT	en	O
@payalinsan15	rest	O
:	rest	O
@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#MSG2RocksPunjab	rest	O
Mehak	hi	B-PERSON
aa	hi	O
rhi	hi	O
hai	hi	O
...	rest	O
Fiza	hi	B-PERSON
bhi	hi	O
Ga	hi	O
rhi	hi	O
h	hi	O
...	rest	O
Waahhh	rest	O

RT	en	O
@HarishK25173278	rest	O
:	rest	O
@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#JaameInsanDivas	rest	O
Saari	hi	O
Kyanat	hi	O
ko	hi	O
Aaj	hi	O
ke	hi	O
Din	hi	O
ki	hi	O
Mubarkan	rest	O
yo	hi	O
...	rest	O
https://t.co/JffOjGKoey	en	O
#TheIrfanism	en	O

@cricketwallah	en	O
sir	hi	O
Khawaja	hi	B-PERSON
likhe	hi	O
wanna	hi	O
@Uz_Khawaja	hi	O
bura	hi	O
man	hi	O
Jayega	hi	O
...	rest	O
Hahahahaha	rest	O
https://t.co/WGej73XbCk	en	O

RT	en	O
@kalakaaar	hi	O
:	rest	O
Arrest	en	O
sonakshi	rest	B-PERSON
sinha	rest	I-PERSON
for	en	O
mimicking	en	O
Buffalo	en	O
.	rest	O
y	en	O
"	rest	O
plz	en	O
soch	hi	O
samajh	hi	O
k	hi	O
likha	hi	O
karo	hi	O
.	rest	O

@jaman_04	rest	O
@PujaaGhosh	hi	O
Happy	en	O
mahashivratri	rest	O
om	rest	O
namah	rest	O
shivay	en	B-PERSON
.	rest	O

Nestle	en	B-ORGANISATION
brings	en	O
back	en	O
Maggi	en	O
noodles	en	O
,	rest	O
starts	en	O
market	en	O
rollout	en	O
#MaggiKiGharWapsi	hi	O
#Happy	hi	O
#AacheDin	hi	O

RT	en	O
@SalmanzShona	rest	O
:	rest	O
Up	en	O
-	rest	O
MulayamSingh	rest	B-PERSON
-	rest	O
-	rest	O
?	rest	O
Mulayam	rest	B-PERSON

@VishalDadlani	rest	O
Sir	hi	O
aapke	hi	O
#MannKiBaat	hi	O
toh	hi	O
#PanamaLeaks	rest	O
me	hi	O
hi	hi	O
pata	hi	O
chal	hi	O
gaya	hi	O
tha	hi	O
.	rest	O

RT	en	O
@YuvaiTV	en	O
:	rest	O
Tyagi	hi	B-PERSON
and	en	O
Khaitan	rest	B-PERSON
are	en	O
examples	en	O
of	en	O
'	rest	O
Behti	hi	O
Ganga	hi	O
me	hi	O
Haath	hi	O
Dho	hi	O
lena	hi	O
'	rest	O
:	rest	O
RM	rest	O
@manoharparrikar	rest	O
in	en	O
LS	en	O
#AgustaWestlandScam	en	O
https://t.co/	rest	O

Who	en	O
is	en	O
the	en	O
best	en	O
comedian	en	O
in	en	O
the	en	O
parliament	en	O
after	en	O
Lalu	en	B-PERSON
Prasad	en	I-PERSON
Yadav	rest	I-PERSON
.	rest	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
.	rest	O
#ComedianInParliament	en	O

*	rest	O
JAI_SHIV_SHANKAR	rest	O
*	rest	O
SOHBAT	rest	B-PLACE
PUR	rest	I-PLACE
ki	hi	O
Tamam	hi	O
Hindu	rest	O
brodry	en	O
ko	hi	O
"	rest	O
MAHASHIVRATRI	rest	O
"	rest	O
KI	hi	O
LAKH	hi	O
LAKH	hi	O
BHADAI	hi	O
DETE	hi	O
HAIN	hi	O
,	rest	O
BY	en	O
>	rest	O
Ajeet	rest	B-PERSON
panjwani	rest	I-PERSON
&	rest	O
Deepak	rest	B-PERSON
Talreja	rest	I-PERSON
.	rest	O

@PRATIKatron	en	O
High	en	O
End	en	O
PC	rest	O
hai	hi	O
kya	hi	O
?	rest	O
o.O	rest	O
mera	hi	O
to	hi	O
4	rest	O
saal	hi	O
phle	hi	O
hi	hi	O
obsolete	en	O
ho	hi	O
gaya	hi	O
tha	hi	O
:(	rest	O

Gyan	hi	O
ki	hi	O
3	rest	O
Baate	hi	O
hmesa	hi	O
yad	hi	O
rkhna	hi	O
Gyan	en	O
no	en	O
1	rest	O
:	rest	O
Agar	hi	O
koi	hi	O
hume	hi	O
accha	hi	O
lagta	hi	O
hai	hi	O
to	hi	O
accha	hi	O
wo	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
hum	hi	O
hai	hi	O
...	rest	O
Aur	hi	O
agar	hi	O
...	rest	O
http://t.co/mcInUfjWK1	en	O

@friendscongress	en	O
aag	hi	O
lagane	hi	O
wala	hi	O
likha	hi	O
lekin	hi	O
@AnupamPkher	rest	O
ji	hi	O
ye	hi	O
bhi	hi	O
kahe	hi	O
ki	hi	O
jis	hi	O
din	hi	O
@OfficeOfRG	en	O
PM	rest	O
ke	hi	O
1/10	rest	O
ho	hi	O
jayege	hi	O
,	rest	O
he	en	O
will	en	O
vote	en	O
for	en	O
him	en	O
.	rest	O

#MahaShivratri	rest	O
he	hi	O
shankar	hi	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
hindu	rest	O
samaj	hi	O
ke	hi	O
raksha	hi	O
karo	hi	O
,	rest	O
bharat	rest	B-PLACE
bhumi	hi	O
ke	hi	O
raksha	hi	O
karo	hi	O
,	rest	O
gau	rest	O
ma	hi	O
or	hi	O
dharm	hi	O
ke	hi	O
raksha	hi	O
karo	hi	O
,	rest	O
adharm	hi	O
ka	hi	O
nash	hi	O
karo	hi	O
.	rest	O

@ArvindKejriwal	en	O
#WhereIsRahul	en	O
#Pappu	rest	O
toh	hi	O
Gaya	hi	O
Sonia	rest	B-PERSON
Mai	hi	O
apko	hi	O
cong	en	B-ORGANISATION
chief	en	O
bana	hi	O
sakti	hi	O
hai	hi	O
shayad	hi	O
.	rest	O
Kyonki	hi	O
beta	hi	O
Pappu	rest	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
#DakuDamaad	rest	O
ur	en	O
d	en	O
nly	en	O
option	en	O

*	rest	O
whistle's	en	O
main	hi	O
hoon	hi	O
na	hi	O
tune	hi	O
*	rest	O
#12YearsOfMainHoonNa	en	O

RT	en	O
@PerennialCold	en	O
:	rest	O
@aashish81us	rest	O
@BhagwanUvach	en	O
It	en	O
happened	en	O
within	en	O
500	rest	O
meters	en	O
of	en	O
Akhiles	en	B-PERSON
pappu	en	B-PERSON
residence	en	O
.	rest	O
UP-Bihar	rest	B-PLACE
has	en	O
become	en	O
jungle	hi	O
raaj	hi	O

@ETNOWlive	en	O
@sagarikaghose	hi	O
Pappu	rest	B-PERSON
ka	hi	O
ek	hi	O
aur	hi	O
interview	en	O
Arnab	hi	B-PERSON
se	hi	O
karwao	hi	O
...	rest	O
Pata	hi	O
chal	hi	O
jayega	hi	O
@ArnabGoswami	hi	O

http://t.co/wlEypxmWrd	en	O
:	rest	O
Education	en	O
portal	en	O
#RailBudget2015	en	O
#AFGvSCO	en	O
#LandBillWar	rest	O
#EndVVIPRaj	rest	O
#IREvUAE	en	O
Suresh	en	B-PERSON
Prabhu	rest	I-PERSON
Vinay	rest	B-PERSON
Kumar	hi	I-PERSON
Shaiman	hi	B-PERSON
Anwar	hi	I-PERSON

RT	en	O
@BeingSalmanKhan	en	O
:	rest	O
Te	hi	O
Marjaava	hi	O
Te	hi	O
Marjaava	hi	O
Te	hi	O
Marjaavaaaaannaa	hi	O
https://t.co/rqOdxKZ8Wt	en	O

CM	rest	O
@Dev_Fadnavis	rest	O
&	rest	O
I	en	O
held	en	O
wide-ranging	en	O
discussions	en	O
on	en	O
the	en	O
drought	en	O
in	en	O
parts	en	O
of	en	O
Maharashtra	hi	B-PLACE
...	rest	O
https://t.co/j9Ym0CA4M4	en	O
via	en	O
@VishalBhardiya	hi	O

"	rest	O
Bewafa	hi	O
duniya	hi	O
mein	hi	O
kon	hi	O
sari	hi	O
zindagi	hi	O
sath	hi	O
de	hi	O
ga	hi	O
tera	hi	O
.	rest	O
*	rest	O
*	rest	O
Log	hi	O
to	hi	O
hathon	hi	O
se	hi	O
dafnaa	hi	O
kar	hi	O
bhool	hi	O
jate	hi	O
hain	hi	O
k	hi	O
Qabar	hi	O
konsi	hi	O
thi	hi	O
......	rest	O

Style	en	O
Redefined	en	O
MegaStar	en	O
\m/	rest	O
Arachakammm	hi	O
https://t.co/WiSR8eYa5n	en	O

@StarSportsIndia	en	O
#matchpoint	en	O
best	en	O
opener	en	O
Ajinkiya	hi	B-PERSON
Rahane	hi	I-PERSON
consistent	en	O
effective	en	O
trustworthy	en	O
classy	en	O
!!	rest	O

@anumuae	rest	O
LOL	rest	O
,	rest	O
Pehle	hi	O
tum	hi	O
log	hi	O
tumhari	hi	O
Kom	hi	O
walo	hi	O
ko	hi	O
samjhao	hi	O
ki	hi	O
Atankwadi	hi	O
banna	hi	O
choad	hi	O
de	hi	O

RT	en	O
@harakhpadudo	rest	O
:	rest	O
@sagarcasm	rest	O
Obama	rest	B-PERSON
to	hi	O
modi	rest	B-PERSON
on	en	O
phone	en	O
:	rest	O
happy	en	O
Diwali	hi	O
Modi	rest	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
Thank	en	O
you	en	O
Obama	rest	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
you	en	O
are	en	O
welcome	en	O
..	rest	O
Modi	rest	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
ya	hi	O
sure	en	O
..	rest	O
after	en	O
UK	en	B-PLACE
visit	en	O
...	rest	O

Srilanka	rest	B-PLACE
won	en	O
because	en	O
of	en	O
#NaMo	rest	O
in	en	O
their	en	O
National	en	O
Anthem	en	O
.	rest	O
#SLvsInd	en	O
#IndvSL	rest	O
#wt20final	rest	O
#BJPManifesto	rest	O
Ab	hi	O
ki	hi	O
Baar	hi	O
......	rest	O
;)	rest	O

RT	en	O
@IndianExpress	rest	O
:	rest	O
Live	en	O
#RailBudget2015	en	O
:	rest	O
Swaach	hi	O
Bharat	hi	B-PLACE
Abhiyan	hi	O
will	en	O
be	en	O
implemented	en	O
in	en	O
railways	en	O
.	rest	O
Cleanliness	en	O
is	en	O
a	en	O
priority	en	O
:	rest	O
Prabhu	rest	B-PERSON
http://t	en	O
.	rest	O

Listening	en	O
to	hi	O
@Rishiji	rest	O
https://t.co/CtcvAvAbdk	en	O
#HappyMahaShivratri	rest	O
Mahashivratri	rest	O
ki	hi	O
hardik	hi	O
shubhkaamnaye	hi	O
!	rest	O

@arjunt_92	rest	O
32xx-28xx	rest	O
means	en	O
400	rest	O
so	en	O
from	en	O
2800	rest	O
till	en	O
24xx	rest	O
trade	en	O
is	en	O
valid	en	O
every	en	O
on	en	O
rise	en	O
booking	en	O
on	en	O
100/150	rest	O
dip	hi	O
25%	rest	O
more	en	O
adding	en	O
kind	en	O
of	en	O
,,	rest	O

RT	en	O
@kenanmalik	rest	O
:	rest	O
Worth	en	O
celebrating	en	O
not	en	O
so	en	O
much	en	O
that	en	O
Sadiq	hi	B-PERSON
Khan	hi	I-PERSON
is	hi	O
London's	rest	B-PLACE
first	en	O
Muslim	en	O
mayor	en	O
but	en	O
that	en	O
for	en	O
many	en	O
Londoners	en	O
that	en	O
was	en	O
irrelevan	en	O

@iamrana	rest	O
Bade	hi	O
Muji	hi	O
ko	hi	O
mara	hi	O
Sajde	hi	O
amrah	hi	O
ko	hi	O
gar	hi	O
mara	hi	O
Nihange	hi	O
ajdaho	hi	O
sere	hi	O
nar	hi	O
mara	hi	O
to	hi	O
kya	hi	O
mara	hi	O
.!	rest	O

@DivineSoulAmit	en	O
aap	hi	O
ko	hi	O
bhi	hi	O
Happy	en	O
Mahashivratri	rest	O
Jii	hi	O
:)	rest	O
Om	rest	O
Namaah	rest	O
Shivai	rest	O
!	rest	O

RT	en	O
@sudhirchaudhary	hi	O
:	rest	O
Good	en	O
to	en	O
see	en	O
Manoj	rest	B-PERSON
Kumar	rest	I-PERSON
at	en	O
the	en	O
centrestage	en	O
once	en	O
agn	en	O
!	rest	O
The	en	O
original	en	O
Bharat	hi	B-PERSON
Kumar	hi	I-PERSON
who	en	O
brought	en	O
patriotism	en	O
to	hi	O
IndianCinema	rest	O
h	hi	O

@ankitv	rest	O
-	rest	O
mujhe	hi	O
laptop	en	O
buy	en	O
karna	hi	O
hai	hi	O
in	en	O
which	en	O
brand	en	O
,	rest	O
specification	en	O
aur	hi	O
bettery	en	O
backup	en	O
acha	hi	O
ho	hi	O
..	rest	O
Plzz	en	O
let	en	O
me	hi	O

InshAllah	en	O
they	en	O
are	en	O
going	en	O
to	en	O
get	en	O
out	en	O
before	en	O
70	rest	O
...	rest	O
InshAllah	rest	O
..	rest	O
Meri	hi	O
baddua	hi	O
lgy	hi	O
gi	hi	O
in	hi	O
bhenC	hi	O
ko	hi	O
:	rest	O
@	rest	O
#PakvInd	rest	O

RT	en	O
@tavleen_singh	en	O
:	rest	O
Anurag	en	B-PERSON
Thakur	hi	I-PERSON
asked	en	O
if	en	O
Congress	en	B-ORGANISATION
was	en	O
with	en	O
Afzal	en	B-PERSON
Guru	en	I-PERSON
or	en	O
with	en	O
those	en	O
who	en	O
saved	en	O
Parliament	en	O
.	rest	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
left	en	O
the	en	O
Lok	hi	B-ORGANISATION
Sabha	hi	I-ORGANISATION

Happy	en	O
Mahashivratri	rest	O
.	rest	O
#mahashivratri	rest	O
Shivratri	rest	O
Bhajans	rest	O
By	en	O
Anuradha	rest	B-PERSON
Paudwal	rest	I-PERSON
,	rest	O
Lakhbir	rest	B-PERSON
Singh	rest	I-PERSON
Lakkha	hi	O
I	en	O
Audio	en	O
Song	en	O
...	rest	O
:	rest	O
http://t.co/yJGhzkFe60	en	O

Kyaa	hi	O
Kool	en	O
Hain	hi	O
Hum	hi	O
3	rest	O
-	rest	O
Official	en	O
Trailer	en	O
--	rest	O
Starring	en	O
-	rest	O
Tusshar	hi	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Aftab	rest	B-PERSON
Shivdasani	rest	I-PERSON
and	en	O
Mandana	rest	B-PERSON
Karimi	hi	I-PERSON
https://t.co/XwD19ZBBL8	en	O

@Shah___Khan	rest	O
Rapping	en	O
??	rest	O
Yo	en	O
Yo	en	O
Honey	en	B-PERSON
Singh	en	I-PERSON
ke	hi	O
fan	en	O
ho	hi	O
kya	hi	O
?	rest	O

Doston	en	O
,	rest	O
bhaiayon	hi	O
or	hi	O
bahno	hi	O
meri	hi	O
sarkar	hi	O
aayegi	hi	O
to	hi	O
1year	en	O
ma	en	O
3cr	en	O
berojgaron	en	O
KO	hi	O
naukri	hi	O
dunga	hi	O
...	rest	O
he	hi	O
he	hi	O
#	rest	O
_	rest	O

RT	en	O
@Thakurpops	en	O
:	rest	O
@vaibysays	hi	O
hahahhaa	hi	O
chor	hi	O
ki	hi	O
daadi	hi	O
m	hi	O
tinka	hi	O

Subh	hi	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
,	rest	O
Om	rest	O
namah	rest	O
Sivaya	rest	B-PERSON

Welcoming	en	O
Sooraj	rest	B-PERSON
Barjatya's	rest	I-PERSON
Prem	en	O
again	en	O
#PremRatanDhanPayo	en	O
http://t.co/3KxVwAqn95	en	O

Post-processing	en	O
Shaadi	hi	O
ka	hi	O
shoot	en	O

back	en	O
to	en	O
normal	en	O
routine	en	O
,	rest	O
dala	hi	O
chawal	hi	O
roti	hi	O
for	en	O
BediJi	rest	B-PERSON
#BJP	rest	O
#AAPSweep	rest	O
#DelhiDecides	en	O

#INDvsPAK	rest	O
Afridi	en	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
ab	hi	O
mai	hi	O
ghar	hi	O
ja	hi	O
k	hi	O
kya	hi	O
khuga	hi	O
ki	hi	O
India	rest	B-PLACE
ne	hi	O
maaa	hi	O
chod	hi	O
dii	hi	O

Waking	en	O
up	en	O
with	en	O
mere	hi	O
desh	hi	O
ki	hi	O
dharti	hi	O
....	rest	O
Is	en	O
a	en	O
ritual	en	O
now	en	O
#RepublicDay	en	O

That's	en	O
mine	en	O
epic	en	O
Shame	en	O
on	en	O
Modi	rest	B-PERSON
...!	rest	O
AAP	rest	B-ORGANISATION
Govt	en	O
Venkaiah	rest	B-PERSON
Naidu	rest	I-PERSON
#SansadChalneDo	hi	O
@aartic02	rest	O
https://t.co/2DbnTvFZfj	en	O

Kya	hi	O
#TaherShah	hi	O
khud	hi	O
zinda	hi	O
hai	hi	O
logu	hi	O
ka	hi	O
response	en	O
dekh	hi	O
kar	hi	O
?	rest	O
Ya	hi	O
fir	hi	O
usnay	hi	O
aqal	hi	O
bech	hi	O
di	hi	O
hai	hi	O
?	rest	O

Why	en	O
the	en	O
hell	en	O
#WhereIsRahul	en	O
trending	en	O
are	en	O
ye	hi	O
to	hi	O
Rahul	hi	B-PERSON
aur	hi	O
Sonia	rest	B-PERSON
gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
ko	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
Pata	hi	O
chala	hi	O
tumhein	hi	O
kya	hi	O
khak	hi	O
Pata	hi	O
lagega	hi	O
....	rest	O

Modi	en	B-PERSON
yesterday	en	O
&	rest	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
today	en	O
,	rest	O
needlessly	en	O
long	en	O
speeches	en	O
with	en	O
irritating	en	O
interpreters	en	O
.	rest	O
Consolation	en	O
is	en	O
that	en	O
it	en	O
is	en	O
English	en	O
&	rest	O
not	en	O
Hindi	rest	O
.	rest	O

:	rest	O
LAST	en	O
NIGHT	en	O
MAHASHIVRATRI	rest	O
RUDRABHISHEK	rest	O
.....	rest	O
Abeer	hi	B-PERSON
aur	hi	O
Gulaal	hi	B-PERSON
Sringaar	rest	B-PLACE
....	rest	O
http://t.co/9u3oSE0Lwy	en	O

RT	en	O
@CricketNDTV	en	O
:	rest	O
#AsiaCup	rest	O
India	rest	B-PLACE
:	rest	O
Dhawan	rest	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Rohit	en	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Kohli	rest	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Rahane	hi	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Rayudu	rest	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Karthik	hi	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Jadeja	rest	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Ashwin	en	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Mishra	rest	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Shami	hi	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Bhuvneshwar	hi	B-PERSON
http://t.co/ls5I	en	O

RT	en	O
@trevias_azuis	rest	O
:	rest	O
Congress	en	B-ORGANISATION
:	rest	O
hum	hi	O
chor	hi	O
hai	hi	O
,	rest	O
hum	hi	O
deesh	hi	O
ko	hi	O
loot	hi	O
k	hi	O
kha	hi	O
rahe	hi	O
the	hi	O
.	rest	O
But	en	O
dare	hi	O
u	en	O
raise	en	O
fingers	en	O
upon	en	O
us	hi	O
Desh	hi	O
toh	hi	O
humare	hi	O
baap	hi	O
ka	hi	O
ha	hi	O

RT	en	O
@exasperating_	en	O
:	rest	O
'	rest	O
ammi	hi	O
kal	hi	O
se	hi	O
tatti	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
aye	hi	O
'	rest	O
http://t.co/hNtZNYnAow	en	O

Lala	hi	O
toh	hi	O
gyo	hi	O
!!!	rest	O
Afridi	en	B-PERSON
roasted	en	O
by	en	O
@imVkohli	en	O
#IndvsPak	rest	O
#IndWins	rest	O

RT	en	O
@insan_neha	rest	O
:	rest	O
@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#MustWatchMSG	en	O
ur	en	O
Acting	en	O
Papaa	rest	O
..	rest	O
Masha	hi	O
Allah	hi	O
..	rest	O
Aattttt	hi	O
..	rest	O
Sirraaa	rest	O
No	en	O
words	en	O
Papa	en	O
Love	en	O
You	en	O
..	rest	O
My	en	O
Papa	en	O
The	en	O
Great	en	O
mua	hi	O

RT	en	O
@TimesNow	en	O
:	rest	O
Mehbooba	hi	O
Mufti	en	O
will	en	O
be	en	O
sworn	en	O
in	en	O
as	en	O
the	en	O
first	en	O
woman	en	O
chief	en	O
minister	en	O
of	en	O
Jammu	rest	B-PLACE
&	rest	O
Kashmir	hi	B-PLACE
today	en	O
.	rest	O
Congress	en	B-ORGANISATION
to	en	O
boycott	en	O
ceremony	en	O
#Meh	rest	O

Naam	hi	O
mein	hi	O
hi	hi	O
BT	hi	O
hai	hi	O
.	rest	O
Kaise	hi	O
chalegi	hi	O
BT	rest	O
Brinjal	rest	O
India	rest	B-PLACE
mein	hi	O
bc	rest	O
.	rest	O

RT	en	O
@iamsrk	rest	O
:	rest	O
Kya	hi	O
baat	hi	O
hai	hi	O
...	rest	O
Haryana	hi	B-PLACE
ka	hi	O
Sher	hi	O
aa	hi	O
gaya	hi	O
...	rest	O
Sultan	rest	B-PERSON
Bhaijaan	rest	I-PERSON
https://t.co/PB8JynGyKf	en	O

RT	en	O
@sheshnath99	rest	O
:	rest	O
1950	rest	O
:	rest	O
Muktesvara	en	B-PLACE
is	en	O
10th	en	O
century	en	O
Temple	en	O
of	en	O
Lord	en	O
Shiva	rest	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Bhubaneshwar	hi	B-PLACE
.	rest	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
#Mahadev	rest	O
http://t.co/i7FRZzVX59	en	O
via	en	O
@	rest	O

Time	en	O
for	en	O
another	en	O
wicket	en	O
india	rest	B-PLACE
!	rest	O
#IndvsSA	rest	O

@spanikkal	rest	O
@ankitlal	rest	O
@chetan_bhagat	hi	O
kya	hi	O
bhigo	hi	O
Ke	hi	O
mara	hi	O
hi	hi	O
sir	hi	O
chetan	hi	B-PERSON
Ke	hi	O
,	rest	O
super	en	O
se	hi	O
uppar	en	O
Wala	hi	O
shot	hi	O

RT	en	O
@OYERJALOK	en	O
:	rest	O
And	en	O
the	en	O
Rockkkkk	en	O
is	en	O
Cookingggggggg	en	O
@TheRock	en	O
with	en	O
@priyankachopra	en	O
while	en	O
#Baywatch	en	O
film	en	O
Shoot	en	O
.	rest	O
@baywatchmovie	en	O
#RjAlok	rest	O
https://	rest	O

Happy	en	O
Women's	en	O
day	en	O
to	en	O
wuss	en	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
.	rest	O
#WomensDay	en	O

RT	en	O
@BCCI	rest	O
:	rest	O
Dear	en	O
@virendersehwag	en	O
pa	hi	O
,	rest	O
can	en	O
you	en	O
please	en	O
get	en	O
Nehra	rest	B-PERSON
ji	hi	O
on	en	O
social	en	O
media	rest	O
?	rest	O
https://t.co/3SsWb5hj0h	en	O

Aa	hi	O
Gaye	hi	O
harami	hi	O
pan	hi	O
per	hi	O
ye	hi	O
he	hi	O
hai	hi	O
in	hi	O
ke	hi	O
jaat	hi	O
aur	hi	O
kuch	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
AK	hi	O
aap	hi	O
sucche	hi	O
ho	hi	O
aur	hi	O
such	en	O
ke	hi	O
sath	hi	O
Allah	hi	O
hai	hi	O
.	rest	O
#ModiFearsKejriwal	en	O

@desert_bedouin1	en	O
ishrat	en	B-PERSON
bhi	hi	O
terrorist	en	O
thi	hi	O

RT	en	O
@PrathmeshSawant	en	O
:	rest	O
BJP	rest	B-ORGANISATION
seems	en	O
confused	en	O
between	en	O
"	rest	O
Nirodh	rest	O
"	rest	O
and	en	O
"	rest	O
Virodh	rest	O
"	rest	O
#BJPCountsCondoms	rest	O

RT	en	O
@RpG_89	en	O
:	rest	O
HAHAHHA	rest	O
Arunachal	hi	B-PLACE
bhi	hi	O
Gayi	hi	O
!!	rest	O
Kamal	hi	O
khila	hi	O
Arunachal	hi	B-PLACE
mein	hi	O
:D	rest	O
https://t.co/Sra3yt9qap	en	O

@takshak_speaks	hi	O
Garmi	hi	O
badh	hi	O
gyi	hi	O
hai	hi	O
..	rest	O
Tu	hi	O
bata	hi	O
..	rest	O
Tweet	en	B-ORGANISATION
like	en	O
karna	hi	O
kab	hi	O
shuru	hi	O
karega	hi	O
dobara	hi	O

Vancouver	en	B-PLACE
Nagar	hi	I-PLACE
kirtan	hi	O
dia	hi	O
kuj	hi	O
pics	en	O
..	rest	O

#MSGthoughts	en	O
wooooov	en	O
Salute	en	O
u	en	O
to	hi	O
guru	hi	O
ji	hi	O
@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O

Happy	en	O
Mahashivratri	en	O
to	en	O
all	en	O
friends	en	O
.	rest	O
maulik	rest	B-PERSON
.	rest	O
mb	hi	O
raj_n_ish	rest	O
ajay_vora	rest	O
rajdeepsinhjadeja75	rest	O
jaydipjarsaniya	hi	O
http://t.co/z8O7i59iUc	rest	O

#mahi	rest	O
paai	hi	O
,	rest	O
tussi	hi	O
great	en	O
ho	hi	O
...	rest	O
#tofu	rest	O
kabool	hi	O
karo	hi	O

@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#MustWatchMSG	en	O
Thankyouuu	en	O
Soo	en	O
Muchh	rest	O
Papaa	rest	O
For	en	O
Everything	en	O
...	rest	O
Hamesha	hi	O
Sath	hi	O
Rehna	hi	O
Pa	hi	O
Aapke	hi	O
Bina	hi	O
Mera	hi	O
Koi	hi	O
Nai	hi	O
Hai	hi	O
..	rest	O
Love	en	O
You	en	O
..	rest	O

Raina	rest	B-PERSON
ne	hi	O
Rain	en	O
laga	hi	O
di	hi	O
re	hi	O
bawa	hi	O
#IndvsPak	rest	O

Sub	hi	O
Lok	hi	O
Ek	hi	O
Particular	en	O
day	en	O
pe	hi	O
hi	hi	O
kyu	hi	O
Bhagwanji	hi	O
ko	hi	O
Yaadh	hi	O
karte	hi	O
hai	hi	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
#Ramnavmi	rest	O
#ganeshChaturthi	hi	O
#hanumanjayanti	rest	O

Jammu	rest	B-PLACE
,	rest	O
Bhutan	rest	B-PLACE
,	rest	O
Nepal	rest	B-PLACE
,	rest	O
Laddakh	rest	B-PLACE
.	rest	O
Too	en	O
much	en	O
adventure	en	O
.	rest	O
Samajh	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
aata	hi	O
Motabhai	hi	O
PM	rest	O
bane	hi	O
hain	hi	O
ya	hi	O
Roadie	hi	O
.	rest	O
;)	rest	O
king	en	O
awesome	en	O
"	rest	O
muhaaaaaaaaaa	hi	O

@itsSSR	en	O
@anky1912	rest	O
awwww	rest	O
happy	en	O
birthday	en	O
ankita	hi	B-PERSON
lokhande	hi	I-PERSON
na	hi	O
kar	hi	O
ke	hi	O
Chutti	hi	O
li	hi	O
h	hi	O
#RahulOnLeave	en	O
#	rest	O
@balliawalebaba	rest	O
@choriketweet	en	O
-AD	rest	O

Don't	en	O
knw	en	O
whos	en	O
gonna	en	O
win	en	O
#WT20	rest	O
but	en	O
Afghanistan	en	B-PLACE
already	en	O
won	en	O
hearts	en	O
of	en	O
the	en	O
billions	en	O
...	rest	O
afghan	hi	O
jalebi	hi	O
hahaha	rest	O
#WIvsAFG	en	O
#AFGvWI	en	O
#Cricket	en	O

@jalanpurvi	rest	O
@StarMoviesIndia	rest	O
i	en	O
wish	en	O
ke	hi	O
aap	hi	O
aur	hi	O
main	hi	O
ye	hi	O
contest	en	O
jeete	hi	O

You	en	O
are	en	O
wrong	en	O
Kanhaiya	hi	B-PERSON
!	rest	O
2002	rest	O
Gujarat	rest	B-PLACE
Riots	en	O
and	en	O
1984	rest	O
Sikh	hi	O
Riots	en	O
are	en	O
Different	en	O
:	rest	O
Kanhaiya	hi	B-PERSON
https://t.co/AFOWxmloWT	en	O

@KhanMobeena	hi	O
Kitni	hi	O
Ajeeb	hi	O
hai	hi	O
Gunaaho	hi	O
ki	hi	O
Justuju	hi	O
#Iqbal	rest	O
..!	rest	O
Namaaz	hi	O
bhi	hi	O
jaldi	hi	O
main	hi	O
padtey	hi	O
hain	hi	O
log	hi	O
phir	hi	O
se	hi	O
#gunaah	hi	O
karne	hi	O
k	hi	O
liye	hi	O
..!	rest	O

RT	en	O
@Yamininisha30	rest	O
:	rest	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	hi	I-PERSON
to	hi	O
videshi	hi	O
jata	hi	O
rahana	hi	O
hai	hi	O
,	rest	O
is	hi	O
baar	hi	O
vacations	en	O
ki	hi	O
baat	hi	O
,	rest	O
kuchh	hi	O
daal	hi	O
me	hi	O
kala	hi	O
hai	hi	O
#RahulOnLeave	en	O

#RailBudget2015	rest	O
#PrabhuKiRail	rest	O
"	rest	O
Prabhu	hi	B-PERSON
der	hi	O
aaye	hi	O
par	hi	O
durust	en	O
aaye	hi	O
"	rest	O
This	en	O
budget	en	O
is	en	O
a	en	O
revolution	en	O
in	en	O
Modern	en	O
Indian	rest	B-ORGANISATION
Railways	en	I-ORGANISATION
.	rest	O

@Sadafawanvk	rest	O
@aliaa08	rest	O
@iamsrk	rest	O
@ParineetiChopra	en	O
wow	en	O
wow	en	O
mujhe	hi	O
bulaye	hi	O
v	hi	O
nhi	hi	O

#TanuWedsManuReturns	en	O
(@	rest	O
PVR	en	B-ORGANISATION
Cinemas	en	I-ORGANISATION
in	en	O
Pune	hi	B-PLACE
,	rest	O
Maharashtra	hi	B-PLACE
)	rest	O
https://t.co/eYJWQl4G4j	en	O

To	hi	O
all	en	O
Kashir	hi	O
Panun	rest	O
Herath	en	O
Mubarak	rest	O
.	rest	O
Happy	en	O
Mahashivratri	en	O
to	en	O
All	en	O
.	rest	O
Shiv	hi	B-PERSON
Shashwat	hi	O
Hain	hi	O
,	rest	O
Sthir	en	O
Hain	hi	O
,	rest	O
ShantSalone	hi	O
Hai	hi	O
,	rest	O
Utpatti	en	O
Ke	hi	O
Data	hi	O
,	rest	O
ShivShabhu	rest	O

OM	rest	O
NAMAH	rest	O
SHIVAYA	rest	O
!!!	rest	O
Mahashivratri	rest	O
Live	en	O
Webcast	en	O
with	en	O
H	hi	B-PERSON
.	rest	I-PERSON
H	hi	I-PERSON
.	rest	I-PERSON
SRI	rest	I-PERSON
SRI	rest	I-PLACE
RAVI	rest	I-PERSON
SHANKAR	rest	I-PERSON
from	en	O
BANGALORE	rest	B-PLACE
ASHRAM	rest	I-PLACE
...	rest	O
http://t.co/xtmokgZOAT	en	O

Changed	en	O
the	en	O
channel	en	O
!!	rest	O
Watching	en	O
Chhota	hi	B-PERSON
Bheem	hi	I-PERSON
in	en	O
Pogo	en	B-ORGANISATION
!!!	rest	O
#IndvsSA	rest	O

RT	en	O
@bscamishra	rest	O
:	rest	O
..	rest	O
Jaise	hi	O
Delhi	rest	B-PLACE
waalon	hi	O
ne	hi	O
liya	hi	O
tha	hi	O
..	rest	O
Ab	hi	O
kyon	hi	O
kahte	hi	O
ho	hi	O
#KejriwalSaySorry	en	O
..	rest	O
https://t.co/LTwRdL77zf	en	O

@205HiDeeps	en	O
arey	hi	O
Ashuuu	rest	B-PERSON
sir	hi	O
ki	hi	O
khaas	hi	O
'	rest	O
Twamily	en	O
'	rest	O
ki	hi	O
member	en	O
kyu	hi	O
ni	hi	O
baat	hi	O
krungi	hi	O
yar	hi	O
!	rest	O
Kamaal	hi	O
krte	hi	O
ho	hi	O
ap	hi	O
b	hi	O

"	rest	O
@ATSBB	rest	O
:	rest	O
Rithvik	en	B-PERSON
Aur	hi	O
Asha	hi	B-PERSON
ka	hi	O
Havan	hi	O
khas	hi	O
Mahashivratri	rest	O
par	hi	O
..	rest	O
dekhiyega	hi	O
zarur	hi	O
sirf	hi	O
SBB	hi	O
me	hi	O
2.30	rest	O
Baje	hi	O
http://t.co/w5I8s8xw3C	en	O
"	rest	O
excited	en	O

@newslaundry	en	O
@AbhinandanSekhr	rest	O
awesome	en	O
interview	en	O
.	rest	O
1st	en	O
interview	en	O
whr	en	O
kanaihya	hi	B-PERSON
did	en	O
not	en	O
have	en	O
to	hi	O
say-	hi	O
sub	hi	O
judice	en	O
after	en	O
every	en	O
second	en	O
line	en	O

RT	en	O
@ATSBB	rest	O
:	rest	O
Rithvik	en	B-PERSON
Aur	hi	O
Asha	hi	B-PERSON
ka	hi	O
Havan	hi	O
khas	hi	O
Mahashivratri	rest	O
par	hi	O
..	rest	O
dekhiyega	hi	O
zarur	hi	O
sirf	hi	O
SBB	hi	O
me	hi	O
2.3	rest	O
Baje	hi	O
http://t.co/CvnXEQXAKO	en	O
"	rest	O
omgggggg	en	O

Mahashivratri	rest	O
Rudrapujas	rest	O
in	en	O
Pune	en	B-PLACE
with	en	O
Swami	hi	B-PERSON
Pragyapadji	hi	I-PERSON
.	rest	O
http://t.co/VHIGH5h5km	rest	O

Black	en	O
Suit	en	O
Punjabi	hi	O
Video	en	O
Song	en	O
HD	en	O
Download	en	O
2014	rest	O
by	en	O
Preet	en	B-PERSON
Harpal	en	I-PERSON
ft	en	O
.	rest	O
Fateh	en	O
http://t.co/zuQ8xpXttB	en	O

@msteckchandani	rest	O
@BishanBedi	rest	O
@Rajini_rao63	rest	O
Great	en	O
dialogue	en	O
from	en	O
the	en	O
famous	en	O
#MughaleAzam	en	O
Anarkali	hi	B-PERSON
to	hi	O
Saheb-e	hi	B-PERSON
Alam	hi	I-PERSON

#AfterTakingTwoPegs	en	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
might	en	O
consider	en	O
himself	en	O
as	en	O
Smriti	en	B-PERSON
Irani	rest	I-PERSON
.	rest	O

@askubusk	hi	O
Happy	en	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
:)	rest	O
Krishna	rest	B-PERSON
shiva	rest	B-PERSON
devotee	en	O
ku	hi	O
wish	en	O
panradha	hi	O
paatha	hi	O
happy	en	O
ah	en	O
irukku	en	O
:P	rest	O

we	en	O
will	en	O
wants	en	O
greentea	en	O
,	rest	O
more	en	O
namkeen	en	O
item	en	O
,	rest	O
different	en	O
quality	en	O
rice	en	O
in	en	O
patanjali	rest	B-ORGANISATION
product	en	O
@Ach_Balkrishna	rest	O
@yogrishiramdev	rest	O

Jb	hi	O
ap	hi	O
risk	hi	O
pr	hi	O
sawal	hi	O
yaad	hi	O
krke	hi	O
jao	hi	O
or	hi	O
paper	en	O
me	hi	O
wo	hi	O
sawal	hi	O
lag	hi	O
jae	hi	O
..	rest	O
*_*	rest	O
^_^	rest	O
#	rest	O
_	rest	O

It	en	O
was	en	O
a	en	O
conspiracy	en	O
against	en	O
us	en	O
~	rest	O
Saeed	rest	B-PERSON
Ajmal	rest	I-PERSON
Pehle	hi	O
seedhe	hi	O
haath	hi	O
se	hi	O
bowl	en	O
daal	hi	O
le	hi	O
pagle	hi	O
,	rest	O
fir	hi	O
moo	hi	O
kholna	hi	O
#Pakistan	rest	O
#IndvsPak	rest	O

@Madan_Chikna	rest	O
maine	hi	O
to	hi	O
pahile	hi	O
hi	hi	O
bola	hi	O
tha	hi	O
...	rest	O
ab	hi	O
to	hi	O
retweet	en	O
karde	hi	O
bhai	hi	O
...	rest	O
tabhi	hi	O
logo	hi	O
ko	hi	O
pata	hi	O
chalega	hi	O
..	rest	O
tere	hi	O
jaise	hi	O
follower	en	O
kaha	hi	O
hame	hi	O
..	rest	O

RT	en	O
@InternetHinduz	en	O
:	rest	O
"	rest	O
Sonia	rest	B-PERSON
ji	hi	O
aap	hi	O
corruption	en	O
karo	hi	O
,	rest	O
hum	hi	O
aapke	hi	O
saath	hi	O
hain	hi	O
"	rest	O
@INCIndia	rest	O
workers	en	O
#SoniaRahulHazirHo	rest	O
https://t.co/o4eO3FeX4g	en	O

RT	en	O
@IndiaHistorypic	rest	O
:	rest	O
1880s	rest	O
:	rest	O
Kashi	hi	B-PLACE
Vishwanath	en	I-PLACE
Temple	en	I-PLACE
,	rest	O
Varanasi	rest	B-PLACE
,	rest	O
one	en	O
of	en	O
12	en	O
Jyotirlingas	en	O
of	en	O
Lord	en	O
Shiva	rest	B-PERSON
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
http://t.co/J6L8Y4QmZb	en	O
"	rest	O

RT	en	O
@iG_Butt	en	O
:	rest	O
Men	en	O
are	en	O
from	en	O
"	rest	O
send	en	O
your	en	O
pic	en	O
"	rest	O
Women	en	O
are	en	O
from	en	O
"	rest	O
dekh	hi	O
k	hi	O
delete	en	O
kar	hi	O
dena	hi	O
"	rest	O

RT	en	O
@ggiittiikkaa	hi	O
:	rest	O
Kejriwal	hi	B-PERSON
sir	hi	O
has	hi	O
so	en	O
many	en	O
degrees	en	O
.	rest	O
Yesterday	en	O
he	en	O
slammed	en	O
dharnas	hi	O
.	rest	O
Today	en	O
he	en	O
took	en	O
180	rest	O
degrees	en	O
and	en	O
sat	hi	O
on	hi	O
dharna	hi	O
himself	en	O
http	en	O

Sbi	hi	O
exited	en	O
h	hi	O
k	hi	O
pakistan	rest	B-PLACE
harega	hi	O
...	rest	O
aree	en	O
ye	hi	O
koi	hi	O
nai	hi	O
baat	hi	O
h	hi	O
kya	hi	O
...	rest	O
#IndvsPak	rest	O

Anna	hi	B-PERSON
ki	hi	O
Rajneeti	rest	O
class	en	O
join	en	O
karen	hi	O
aur	hi	O
1	rest	O
sal	hi	O
mai	hi	O
bne	hi	O
CM	rest	O
.	rest	O
#WhereIsRahul	en	O
#RahulOnLeave	en	O
#RSSQuestionsTeresa	en	O

Virat	rest	B-PERSON
Kohli	rest	I-PERSON
is	en	O
used	en	O
to	en	O
making	en	O
good	en	O
partnerships	en	O
with	en	O
the	en	O
sharmas	rest	B-PERSON
:)	rest	O
#IndvsWI	rest	O
#wt20	rest	O

Paaji	hi	O
@sachin_rt	en	O
mujhe	hi	O
bhi	hi	O
reply	en	O
kar	hi	O
do	hi	O
na	hi	O
..	rest	O

@MTVRoadies	en	O
kya	hi	O
chutiya	hi	O
personalties	en	O
he	hi	O
vo	hi	O

RT	en	O
@IndianRailMedia	rest	O
:	rest	O
Karad	rest	B-PLACE
-	rest	O
Chiplun	en	B-PLACE
Railway	en	O
Route	en	O
(	rest	O
112	rest	O
km	hi	O
)	rest	O
1200	rest	O
crore	en	O
Rupess	en	O
planned	en	O
investment	en	O
via	en	O
@abpmajhatv	rest	O
@Narendra_IRTS	rest	O
#RailBudget20	rest	O

@Integrated_me	en	O
sleep	en	O
ka	hi	O
koi	hi	O
shape	en	O
nahi	hi	O
hota	hi	O
sahab	hi	O

@DKhantastic	rest	O
Agar	hi	O
politicians	en	O
ke	hi	O
haath	hi	O
me	hi	O
solution	en	O
na	hi	O
chodte	hi	O
to	hi	O
na	hi	O
Jaat	hi	O
agitation	en	O
hota	hi	O
aur	hi	O
na	hi	O
Kashmir	hi	B-PLACE
ki	hi	O
barbaadi	hi	O
.	rest	O

RT	en	O
@indiantweeter	rest	O
:	rest	O
Pic	en	O
1	rest	O
:	rest	O
Bangladeshi	rest	B-PLACE
holding	en	O
dhoni's	en	B-PERSON
head	en	O
Pic	en	O
2	rest	O
:	rest	O
Dhoni	hi	B-PERSON
holding	en	O
Bangladeshi	rest	B-PLACE
team	en	O
#AsiaCupT20Final	en	O
https://t.co/VqW4Wbtt	en	O

67%	rest	O
more	en	O
funds	en	O
allotted	en	O
for	en	O
passenger	en	O
amenities	en	O
:	rest	O
Suresh	en	B-PERSON
Prabhu	rest	I-PERSON
#RailBudget2015	rest	O

#AAPSweep	rest	O
#DelhiDecides	en	O
I	en	O
m	en	O
decide	en	O
shift	en	O
to	hi	O
delhi	rest	B-PLACE
..	rest	O
free	en	O
water	en	O
,	rest	O
Free	en	O
Ele	en	O
,	rest	O
Free	en	O
wifi	en	O
,	rest	O
Free	en	O
vegi	en	O
,	rest	O
Free	en	O
Education	en	O
,	rest	O
Free	en	O
mufler	en	O
,	rest	O
Free	en	O
Cough	en	O
syrup	en	O
haa	hi	O

Feeling	en	O
bad	en	O
for	en	O
RCB	en	B-ORGANISATION
not	en	O
for	en	O
I	en	O
predicted	en	O
them	en	O
in	en	O
Playoff	en	O
but	en	O
feeling	en	O
bad	en	O
for	en	O
Virat	en	B-PERSON
but	en	O
kudos	en	O
to	en	O
Russell	en	B-PERSON
n	en	O
Yusuf	en	B-PERSON
#IPL2016	rest	O

Sir	hi	O
@krishnabgowda	rest	O
Bhadrappa	rest	B-PLACE
L/O	rest	O
has	en	O
lot	en	O
of	en	O
dust	en	O
pollution	en	O
.	rest	O
Can	en	O
be	en	O
eliminated	en	O
if	en	O
4	rest	O
to	hi	O
5	rest	O
inches	en	O
of	en	O
mud	en	O
are	en	O
cleaned	en	O
on	en	O
sides	en	O
of	en	O
road	en	O
@CJoshi28	rest	O

RT	en	O
@BeerOholic	en	O
:	rest	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
Videos	en	O
-	rest	O
helping	en	O
congress	en	B-ORGANISATION
lose	en	O
'	rest	O
One	en	O
Vote	en	O
Per	en	O
View	en	O
'	rest	O

Chal	hi	O
beta	hi	O
#Selfie	en	O
le	hi	O
le	hi	O
re	hi	O
#SelfieKing	en	O
#Devarsh	en	O
#Kids	en	O
#Instapic	rest	O
@	rest	O
Bhavnagar	hi	B-PLACE
https://t.co/SJEvdhhgzf	en	O

Arvind	en	B-PERSON
Kejriwal	en	I-PERSON
Thanks	en	O
for	en	O
the	en	O
follow	en	O
!	rest	O

RT	en	O
@CMofKarnataka	rest	O
:	rest	O
Congratulations	en	O
to	hi	O
Shri	hi	O
@NitishKumar	hi	O
ji	hi	O
and	en	O
the	en	O
people	en	O
of	en	O
Bihar	rest	B-PLACE
.	rest	O

@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
@derasachasauda	hi	O
jiyge	en	O
marge	en	O
mr	en	O
mitege	en	O
desh	hi	O
k	hi	O
aan	hi	O
ban	hi	O
shan	hi	O
k	hi	O
liy	hi	O
or	hi	O
buraliyo	hi	O
ka	hi	O
khatma	hi	O
khrne	hi	O
k	hi	O
liy	en	O
MSG	en	B-ORGANISATION
tha	hi	O
#MSGmission	en	O

@RabiaAnumm	rest	O
and	en	O
2	rest	O
number	en	O
khan	hi	O
haar	hi	O
gyaa	hi	O

Mahashivratri	rest	O
ki	hi	O
hardik	hi	O
shubkamnayein	hi	O
!	rest	O
Shiva	rest	B-PERSON
the	hi	O
Adiyogi	hi	B-PERSON
'	rest	O
may	en	O
every1	en	O
be	en	O
blessed	en	O
with	en	O
the	en	O
grace	en	O
of	en	O
meditation	en	O
.	rest	O
Om	rest	O
!	rest	O
Om	rest	O
!	rest	O
Om	rest	O
Namah	rest	O
Shivaya	rest	O
:)	rest	O

@MehrTarar	hi	O
kash	hi	O
ye	hi	O
songs	rest	O
apki	hi	O
awaz	hi	O
me	hi	O
sun	hi	O
pata	hi	O

RT	en	O
@Ankitaaa_	rest	O
:	rest	O
THOK	hi	O
DIYAAAA	hi	O
!!	rest	O
130	rest	O
RUNS	rest	O
!!	rest	O
CONGRATS	en	O
TEAM	en	O
INDIA	rest	B-PLACE
#IndVsSA	rest	O

Kayakalp	hi	B-ORGANISATION
to	hi	O
help	en	O
in	en	O
Technology	en	O
Upgradation	en	O
-	rest	O
Suresh	en	B-PERSON
Prabhu	rest	I-PERSON
#RailBudget2015	rest	O

RT	en	O
@AfsanaMeet	rest	O
:	rest	O
@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#200DaysMSG2	en	O
congrats	en	O
naanu	rest	O
papa	en	O

RT	en	O
AAP_Najafgarh	hi	B-ORGANISATION
"	rest	O
RT	en	O
DocVatsa	en	O
:	rest	O
Modi	rest	B-PERSON
police	en	O
is	en	O
stooping	en	O
so	en	O
low	en	O
targeting	en	O
revered	en	O
veterans	en	O
.	rest	O
And	en	O
Mallaya	en	B-PERSON
was	en	O
helped	en	O
t	en	O
https://t.co/cWoYRGNkKT	en	O
"	rest	O

@kanhaiyajnusu	hi	O
Tumse	hi	O
naa	hi	O
ho	hi	O
payega	hi	O
Beta	hi	O
..	rest	O
Bas	hi	O
Tu	hi	O
BCgiri	hi	O
kar	hi	O
sakta	hi	O
hai	hi	O
.	rest	O
.	rest	O
@KirronKherBJP	rest	O

@Barbiedawra	rest	O
@Rinkkyy	en	O
hiii	en	O
dear	en	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
enjoy	en	O
ur	en	O
day	en	O
yssss	en	O
same	en	O
mene	hi	O
bhi	hi	O
kaha	hi	O
rinkuu	en	B-PERSON
ne	hi	O
bahot	hi	O
din	hi	O
baaad	hi	O
tweet	en	O
kiya	hi	O
hamko	hi	O

@iam_Bhavya	hi	O
itni	hi	O
padhai	hi	O
:-(	rest	O
oye	hi	O
writer	en	O
to	hi	O
ban	hi	O
gaye	hi	O
kyunki	hi	O
thoda	hi	O
bahut	hi	O
waqt	hi	O
to	hi	O
doc	rest	O
.	rest	O
aur	hi	O
eng	en	O
.	rest	O
bhi	hi	O
nikal	hi	O
lete	hi	O
hain	hi	O
:-)	rest	O

@kamaalrkhan	hi	O
tumhara	hi	O
kaam	hi	O
hi	hi	O
yahi	hi	O
hai	hi	O
sir	hi	O
g	en	O

@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#MSGSocialWelfare	en	O
great	en	O
papa	en	O
ji	hi	O
..	rest	O
dhan	hi	O
dhan	hi	O
satguru	hi	B-PERSON
tera	hi	O
hi	hi	O
aasra	hi	O

RT	en	O
muktimohanWeb	en	O
:	rest	O
Watch	en	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
#Tandav	rest	O
performance	en	O
by	en	O
thisIsMukti	en	O
http://t.co/5CihVC8RdC	en	O
MohanShakti	hi	B-PERSON
http://t.co/kWOnNivlEA	en	O

RT	en	O
@MUFCNewsUK	en	O
:	rest	O
Drumlanrig	en	O
:	rest	O
No	en	O
sadomasochism	en	O
in	en	O
the	en	O
library	en	O
|	rest	O
#MUFC	rest	O
#Bristol	rest	O
|	rest	O
#WassupMusicVideo	en	O
#baytahminizliyoruz	en	O
http://t.co/Ok7A3cW4qy	en	O

At	en	O
funeral	en	O
of	en	O
Sahara	hi	B-ORGANISATION
chief's	en	O
mother	en	O
:	rest	O
Amitabh	hi	B-PERSON
to	hi	O
Akhilesh	hi	B-PERSON
https://t.co/P5ofQnTcyf	en	O
https://t.co/b6wHGXL1R5	en	O

Superb	en	B-ORGANISATION
movie	en	I-ORGANISATION
really	en	O
the	en	O
best	en	O
movie	en	O
for	en	O
salman	hi	B-PERSON
khan	hi	I-PERSON
watching	en	O
Bajrangi	rest	B-PERSON
Bhaijaan	rest	I-PERSON

@dkbansalin	rest	O
@AmitShah	rest	O
tere	hi	O
seth	hi	O
farjiwaal	hi	O
,	rest	O
khaansiwaal	hi	O
ko	hi	O
"	rest	O
HAWAN	rest	O
KUND	rest	O
"	rest	O
mein	hi	O
daal	hi	O
kar	hi	O
"	rest	O
HAWAN	rest	O
KARENGE	hi	O
HAWAN	hi	O
KARENGE	hi	O
"	rest	O
@HinduRajyam	rest	O
@hindustanse	rest	O

Happy	en	O
MahaShivratri	rest	O
.....	rest	O
Om	rest	O
Namah	rest	O
Shivay	rest	O
.......	rest	O
Har	hi	O
Har	hi	O
Mahadev	rest	B-PERSON
....	rest	O

!!!!	rest	O
Batman	rest	O
vs	en	O
Superman	en	O
Hindi	en	O
trailer	en	O
https://t.co/yyblevhw4b	en	O

@AAPInNews	rest	O
jb	hi	O
aap	hi	O
khattr	hi	B-PERSON
ji	hi	O
se	hi	O
milo	hi	O
to	hi	O
unhe	hi	O
bs	hi	O
itna	hi	O
keh	hi	O
dena	hi	O
ki	hi	O
"	rest	O
Nehar	rest	O
par	hi	O
,	rest	O
faridabad	rest	B-PLACE
me	hi	O
unauthorized	en	O
colonies	en	O
bhot	hi	O
hai	hi	O
"	rest	O
wo	hi	O
smjh	hi	O
jayenge	hi	O
....	rest	O

@sagarcasm	rest	O
TOI	rest	B-ORGANISATION
should	en	O
renamed	en	O
its	en	O
domain	en	O
to	en	O
semi-nudedotcom	en	O

#AAP	rest	O
Water	en	O
and	en	O
Power	en	O
bills	en	O
slashes	en	O
.	rest	O
Congress	en	B-ORGANISATION
and	en	O
BJP	rest	B-ORGANISATION
ka	hi	O
'	rest	O
Vilap	rest	O
'	rest	O
.	rest	O
'	rest	O
Rudali	rest	O
'	rest	O
ban	hi	O
gayi	hi	O
hai	hi	O
dono	hi	O
party	en	O
.	rest	O
#BJP	rest	O
#RailBudget2015	rest	O
#	rest	O

RT	en	O
@shrishtimona	rest	O
:	rest	O
Lee	hi	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Kyunki	hi	O
leader	en	O
gya	hi	O
.	rest	O

@narendramodi	rest	O
#RailBudget2015	en	O
a	en	O
big	en	O
disappointment	en	O
being	en	O
an	en	O
Andhrite	en	O
.	rest	O
God	en	O
sud	en	O
save	en	O
andhra	rest	B-PLACE
&	rest	O
telugu	en	O
people	en	O
.	rest	O
Forced	en	O
unequal	en	O
division	en	O
on	en	O
us	en	O
.	rest	O

Maha	hi	O
Shivrati	hi	O
Shubh	hi	O
Ho	hi	O
....	rest	O
Om	rest	O
Namah	rest	O
Shivay	rest	O
..	rest	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O

@Shaheer_S	rest	O
Gud	en	O
mrng	en	O
nd	en	O
HAPPY	en	O
MAHASHIVRATRI	rest	O
.......	rest	O
SUNO	hi	O
aaj	hi	O
mndir	hi	O
zarur	hi	O
jana	hi	O
jo	hi	O
bhi	hi	O
mangoge	en	O
vo	hi	O
milega	hi	O
...	rest	O

Dhoni	hi	B-PERSON
bhai	hi	O
..	rest	O
thoda	hi	O
dhang	hi	O
se	hi	O
maaro	hi	O
ball	hi	O
ko	hi	O
.	rest	O
:P	rest	O
#indvspak	rest	O
#WC2015	rest	O

@deespeak	hi	O
ko	hi	O
peda	hi	O
kisi	hi	O
or	hi	O
ne	hi	O
kiya	hi	O
,	rest	O
pala	hi	O
kisi	hi	O
or	hi	O
ne	hi	O
,	rest	O
use	en	O
koi	hi	O
or	hi	O
kar	hi	O
raha	hi	O
he	hi	O
or	hi	O
jhel	hi	O
pura	hi	O
desh	hi	O
raha	hi	O
he	hi	O
Incredible	en	O
India	rest	B-PLACE
#LandAcquisitionBill	rest	O

RT	en	O
@subhendujee	rest	O
:	rest	O
The	en	O
CBI	en	B-ORGANISATION
case	en	O
against	en	O
Arvind	en	B-PERSON
Kejriwal's	en	I-PERSON
principal	en	O
secy	en	O
Rajendra	rest	B-PERSON
Kumar	rest	I-PERSON
seems	en	O
to	en	O
be	en	O
falling	en	O
apart	en	O
.	rest	O
https://t.co/DI6Xf6Jo5e	rest	O

@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#MSG	en	O
Says	en	O
papaji	en	O
thanks	en	O
4	en	O
blessings	en	O
and	en	O
launching	en	O
products	en	O
on	en	O
world	en	O
health	en	O
day	en	O
.	rest	O
Den	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
de	hi	O
sakte	hi	O
aapka	hi	O
.	rest	O

SARBJIT	rest	O
Theatrical	en	O
Trailer	en	O
-	rest	O
Aishwarya	hi	B-PERSON
Rai	hi	I-PERSON
Bachchan	hi	I-PERSON
,	rest	O
Randeep	rest	B-PERSON
Hooda	rest	I-PERSON
,	rest	O
Omung	en	B-PERSON
Kumar	en	I-PERSON
https://t.co/932EJbQEsv	en	O

yadav	rest	B-PERSON
ji	hi	O
on	en	O
track	en	O
.	rest	O
hail	rest	O
sir	hi	O
jadejaa	hi	B-PERSON
..	rest	O
:)	rest	O
#indvspak	rest	O

@SrBachchan	hi	O
aaj	hi	O
kal	hi	O
bahut	hi	O
sabko	hi	O
mil	hi	O
gaya	hi	O
hai	hi	O
naya	hi	O
topic	en	O
ki	hi	O
aap	hi	O
par	hi	O
faltu	hi	O
ka	hi	O
ilzam	en	O
lagana	hi	O
!	rest	O
Koi	hi	O
kaam	hi	O
toh	hi	O
hai	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
bas	hi	O
samay	hi	O
betwana	hi	O
hai	hi	O
!	rest	O
ill	en	O
ppl	en	O

RT	en	O
@eastwoodmcfly	en	O
:	rest	O
RIP	rest	O
Schumer's	en	B-PERSON
Amazing	en	O
Acceptance	en	O
Speech	en	O
#GoldenGlobes	en	O
https://t.co/9yic9QbbtH	en	O

I	en	O
expect	en	O
National	en	O
Award	en	O
for	en	O
Shah	hi	B-PERSON
Rukh	hi	I-PERSON
after	en	O
Fan	en	O
:	rest	O
Maneesh	rest	B-PERSON
Sharma	rest	I-PERSON
ViralsDaily	en	O
-	rest	O
https://t.co/9qPotuLtPQ	en	O

Mauka	hi	O
Mauka	hi	O
...	rest	O
Chak	hi	O
De	hi	O
India	rest	B-PLACE

Mushfiqur's	en	B-PERSON
celebration	en	O
soon	en	O
to	en	O
become	en	O
the	en	O
gif	en	O
version	en	O
of	en	O
don't	en	O
count	en	O
your	en	O
chickens	en	O
before	en	O
they	en	O
hatch	en	O
#IndvsBan	rest	O

@nimrah307	en	O
Aisy	en	O
relationships	en	O
ko	hi	O
breakup	en	O
hi	hi	O
hona	hi	O
chahy	hi	O
jo	hi	O
gudmorning	en	O
aur	hi	O
gudnigh	hi	O
k	hi	O
mauhtaj	hi	O
hn	hi	O
:-p	rest	O

Sh	hi	O
.	rest	O
Suresh	en	B-PERSON
Prabhu	hi	I-PERSON
announced	en	O
Malaviya	rest	O
Chair	rest	O
at	en	O
IIT/BHU	rest	B-ORGANISATION
for	en	O
Railway	en	B-ORGANISATION
technology	en	O
#RailBudget2015	en	O

Wishing	en	O
a	en	O
happy	en	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
Om	rest	O
Namah	rest	O
Shivaya	rest	B-PERSON
Om	rest	O
Mrityunjay	en	B-PERSON
mahadev	en	I-PERSON
namosthuthe	en	O
http://t.co/42atPVVVLF	en	O

RT	en	O
@ImVKohlisAngel	en	O
:	rest	O
@RainaKiGudia	rest	O
Awwwww	rest	O
cutuuuuu	en	O
....	rest	O
Thankuuuu	en	O
love	en	O
...	rest	O
Good	en	O
night	en	O

@sud_tyagi	en	O
@iamsrk	rest	O
@FarOutAkhtar	rest	O
@ritesh_sid	en	O
Choriyan	en	O
pahn	en	O
lo	hi	O
farhan	hi	B-PERSON
srk	en	B-PERSON
ritesh	en	B-PERSON
begairato	en	O
tumhari	hi	O
film	en	O
cenima	en	O
me	hi	O
dekhne	hi	O
like	en	O
nahi	hi	O

Koi	hi	O
milne	hi	O
hi	hi	O
ajaye	hi	O
KARACHI	hi	B-ORGANISATION
UNIVERSITY	en	I-ORGANISATION
ir	en	O
kuple	en	O
https://t.co/MkRvbNY4VW	en	O
#occupygezi	en	O
#direngeziparkigeliyoruz	en	O
#YandasMedyaLimonSatOnurluYasa	en	O

#NahiPata	hi	O
sohni	hi	O
Kurian	rest	O
Kahan	hi	O
Chali	hi	O
gae	hi	O
hain	hi	O
:p	rest	O

RT	en	O
@kchowdhury9	en	O
:	rest	O
#boycottraees	en	O
ye	hi	O
movie	en	O
ab	hi	O
nehi	hi	O
lana	hi	O

33	en	O
rd	en	O
tym	en	O
today	en	O
Perfect	en	O
sunday	en	O
watching	en	O
Yeh	hi	O
Jawaani	hi	O
Hai	hi	O
Deewani	hi	O

@PujaaVarma	rest	O
bra	en	O
pahna	hi	O
karo	hi	O
aunty	en	O
!	rest	O

RT	en	O
@UmeSalmaa	en	O
:	rest	O
Team	en	O
India	rest	B-PLACE
to	hi	O
BJP	rest	B-ORGANISATION
"	rest	O
Itna	hi	O
bura	hi	O
toh	hi	O
hum	hi	O
bhi	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
haare	hi	O
"	rest	O
Err:508	rest	O
#AAPSweep	rest	O
#DelhiDecides	en	O

RT	en	O
@rameshsrivats	en	O
:	rest	O
Back	en	O
to	en	O
Bangalore	en	B-PLACE
.	rest	O
37	rest	O
degrees	en	O
.	rest	O
Approximately	en	O
37	en	O
degrees	en	O
more	en	O
than	en	O
Modi	en	B-PERSON
has	en	O
.	rest	O

@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#GratitudeToAllMothers	en	O
Amazing	en	O
video	en	O
pita	hi	O
ji	hi	O
Love	en	O
u	en	O
lot	en	O

India's	rest	B-PLACE
#ThatCricketingMoment	en	O
which	en	O
starts	en	O
after	en	O
the	en	O
dismissals	en	O
of	en	O
Rohit	en	B-PERSON
,	rest	O
Dhawan	rest	B-PERSON
&	rest	O
Raina	rest	B-PERSON
.	rest	O

@itsyaboyladin	en	O
@BeelaalTariq	hi	O
aaj	hi	O
last	en	O
day	en	O
hai	hi	O
screening	en	O
ka	hi	O
?	rest	O

RT	en	O
JasvirSjasvir	rest	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
RT	en	O
jsingh341	en	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
RT	en	O
insan_paul	en	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
RT	en	O
ChandniGodara	rest	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
:	rest	O
5	rest	O
crore	en	O
followers	en	O
of	en	O
Gurmeetramrahim	en	B-PERSON
#MustWatchMSG	en	O
for	en	O
d	en	O
sake	hi	O
of	en	O
promise	en	O

Team	en	O
tht	en	O
#Photowalks	en	O
2gthr	en	O
stays	en	O
2gthr	en	O
:)	rest	O
Suppa	en	O
#PhotoWok	en	O
at	en	O
Dadar	en	B-PLACE
market	en	O
@mehulgohil	en	O
@TheSynergy5	en	O
@wokthiswayindia	en	O
https://t.co/PCye4BOoWq	en	O

@zzoker	en	O
it	en	O
means	en	O
apka	hi	O
chutya	hi	O
katna	hi	O
tay	en	O
he	en	O
#experience	en	O

RT	en	O
@bhars97	rest	O
:	rest	O
Ek	hi	O
jaan	hi	O
hai	hi	O
bhale	hi	O
do	hi	O
badan	hi	O
ho	hi	O
juda	hi	O
Meri	hi	O
hoke	hi	O
hamesha	hi	O
hi	hi	O
rehna	hi	O
kabhi	hi	O
na	hi	O
kehna	hi	O
alvida	hi	O
#VishAna	rest	O
https://t.co/DJp2lNCbkw	rest	O

MP	rest	O
ke	hi	O
UJJAIN	rest	B-PLACE
mein	hi	O
mahashivratri	hi	O
ke	hi	O
avsar	hi	O
par	hi	O
milabati	hi	O
prasad	hi	O
khan	hi	O
se	hi	O
1500	rest	O
vyakti	hi	O
bimar	hi	O
ho	hi	O
gaye	hi	O
jinhe	hi	O
jile	hi	O
ke	hi	O
vibhin	en	O
hospital	en	O
me	hi	O
admit	en	O
hona	hi	O
p	hi	O

@RoyalThough	en	O
baaraat	hi	O
me	hi	O
aayi	hi	O
h	hi	O
kya	hi	O
.	rest	O
Kis	hi	O
baat	hi	O
ka	hi	O
award	hi	O
.	rest	O
Ek	hi	O
toh	hi	O
NRI	rest	O
upar	hi	O
se	hi	O
award	hi	O
?	rest	O
Chal	hi	O
bhaag	hi	O

RT	en	O
@LALETTAN_BOYS	en	O
:	rest	O
Lalettan	rest	B-PERSON
may	en	O
do	en	O
a	en	O
film	en	O
with	en	O
Thala	hi	B-PERSON
in	en	O
Tamil	en	O
for	en	O
Vishnuvardhan	en	B-PERSON
movie	en	O
.	rest	O
Director	en	O
now	en	O
at	en	O
Kerala	rest	B-PLACE
For	en	O
story	en	O
narration	en	O

@Harysforu	en	O
unmatchable	en	O
energy	en	O
eyyyyy	en	O
jai	hi	O
balayya	hi	O

@DareToZlaataan	hi	O
humse	hi	O
ummeed	en	O
na	hi	O
rkho	hi	O
:p	rest	O

@sulabhpandey_	rest	O
@sanjaynirupam	rest	O
@DrunkVinodMehta	en	O
havai	hi	O
yatra	hi	O
se	hi	O
yad	hi	O
aaya	hi	O
!	rest	O
Kahi	hi	O
aap	hi	O
ex	en	O
president	en	O
pratibha	rest	B-PERSON
patil	en	I-PERSON
ji	hi	O
ki	hi	O
to	hi	O
bat	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
kar	hi	O
rahe	hi	O
?	rest	O

He	hi	O
is	hi	O
a	hi	O
real	en	O
guru	en	O
of	en	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
.	rest	O
We	en	O
need	en	O
to	en	O
stop	en	O
blaming	en	O
a	en	O
kid	en	O
when	en	O
we	en	O
have	en	O
a	en	O
guru	en	O
.	rest	O
#ShameOnDigvijaya	rest	O

RT	en	O
@gouravgg1993	en	O
:	rest	O
@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#MSGmissionHumanity	en	O
woww	en	O
pita	hi	O
ji	hi	O
sabhi	hi	O
sewadar	hi	O
apki	hi	O
rehmat	hi	O
se	hi	O
bahut	hi	O
sewa	hi	O
krte	hi	O
hai	hi	O
ji	hi	O

@anilgupta5113	rest	O
@TarekFatah	hi	O
@htTweets	en	O
20	rest	O
million	en	O
ghuse	hi	O
pade	hi	O
hain	hi	O
...	rest	O
diplomacy	en	O
karte	hi	O
rahe	hi	O
to	hi	O
jeena	hi	O
haram	hi	O
ho	hi	O
jayega	hi	O
hamara	hi	O

Need	en	O
one	en	O
for	en	O
Zardari	hi	B-PERSON
and	en	O
Nawaz	rest	B-PERSON
Shareef	rest	I-PERSON
!!	rest	O
https://t.co/6283x5zkZt	en	O

RT	en	O
@ShirishKunder	rest	O
:	rest	O
Aamir	hi	B-PERSON
Khan's	rest	I-PERSON
statement	en	O
.	rest	O
Bhakts	hi	O
can	en	O
wait	en	O
for	en	O
the	en	O
Braille	en	O
version	en	O
.	rest	O
https://t.co/jJFFhXPOMH	rest	O

@BCCI	rest	O
you	en	O
will	en	O
never	en	O
retire	en	O
from	en	O
our	en	O
hearts	en	O
Sachin	en	B-PERSON
..	rest	O
#ThankYouSachin	hi	O

@muzikman_07	rest	O
mohit	hi	B-PERSON
raina	rest	I-PERSON
is	en	O
the	en	O
new	en	O
hottie	en	O

@itsSSR	en	O
fan's	en	O
ki	hi	O
wajse	hi	O
aaj	hi	O
tum	hi	O
aaha	hi	O
tak	hi	O
aaye	hi	O
ho	hi	O
beta	hi	O

@veejay_k	rest	O
@is_ishita	rest	O
@cdc9b75a7795437	rest	O
@nehaa141	rest	O
@sumit24verma	en	O
Mahashivratri	rest	O
ki	hi	O
bahut	hi	O
bahut	hi	O
subhkamnayein	hi	O
to	hi	O
all	en	O
of	en	O
U	en	O
http://t.co/djwlgRSr0f	en	O

#RailBudget2015	rest	O
@narendramodi	rest	O
@RailMinIndia	rest	O
kaamchori	hi	O
/mismanagement/nonsensical	en	O
rules	en	O
/	rest	O
babugiri/	rest	O
all	en	O
this	en	O
sums	en	O
up	en	O
as	en	O
INDIAN	en	B-ORGANISATION
RAILWAY	en	I-ORGANISATION

PIB_India	rest	B-ORGANISATION
#UHF	rest	O
RT	en	O
RailMinIndia	rest	B-ORGANISATION
:	rest	O
67%	rest	O
more	en	O
funds	en	O
allotted	en	O
for	en	O
passenger	en	O
amenities	en	O
#RailBudget2015	en	O
Catch	en	O
it	en	O
live	en	O
http://t.co/Yurj6O5LMW	en	O

@king_ranjhna	rest	O
@21century_kant	en	O
ye	hi	O
respect	en	O
h	hi	O
ek	hi	O
woman	en	O
ki	hi	O
kamal	hi	O
h	hi	O

@ZoomTV	en	O
who	en	O
is	en	O
harman	rest	B-PERSON
baweja	rest	I-PERSON
??	rest	O

@anky1912	rest	O
@itsssr	en	O
Happy	en	O
mahashivratri	rest	O
...	rest	O
aum	hi	O
Namah	rest	O
shivaya	rest	B-PERSON
...	rest	O
"	rest	O

RT	en	O
@SomaVisal	en	O
:	rest	O
#ScamQueenOnRoad	en	O
The	en	O
Sherni	hi	O
became	en	O
a	hi	O
meek	hi	O
cat	en	O
at	en	O
the	en	O
LS	en	B-ORGANISATION
after	en	O
Parikkar's	rest	B-PERSON
concluding	en	O
speech	en	O
?	rest	O
What	en	O
a	en	O
hit	en	O
that	en	O
ran	en	O
away	en	O
virtu	en	O

maan	hi	O
karate	hi	O
superb	en	O
movie	en	O
enjoying	en	O
with	en	O
sivakarthikeyan	en	B-PERSON
comedy	en	O
and	en	O
his	en	O
centiment	en	O

Passport	en	O
.	rest	O
Photo	en	O
.	rest	O
Form	en	O
.	rest	O
Welcome	en	O
to	hi	O
Bhutan	hi	B-PLACE
!	rest	O
#travel	rest	O
#Bhutan	rest	O
@	rest	O
Phuntsholing	en	O
https://t.co/SjlaC0bsc2	rest	O

Shoaib	hi	B-PERSON
malik	en	I-PERSON
showing	en	O
his	en	O
class	en	O
-	rest	O
top	en	O
notch	en	O
-	rest	O
#PAKvsIND	rest	O

RT	en	O
@Mrityunjoykjha	en	O
:	rest	O
My	en	O
fav	en	O
Shiv	hi	B-PERSON
Bhajan	hi	O
"	rest	O
Hari	hi	O
Om	hi	O
Tatsat	hi	O
"	rest	O
by	en	O
Ustad	en	B-PERSON
Bade	hi	I-PERSON
Ghulam	hi	I-PERSON
Ali	hi	I-PERSON
Khan	hi	I-PERSON
Saheb	hi	I-PERSON
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
https://t.co/jxon0VW90l	en	O

HAPPY	en	O
MAHASHIVRATRI	rest	O
<3	rest	O
JAI	hi	O
BHOLENATH	hi	B-PERSON
<3<3	rest	O
JAI	hi	O
MAA	hi	O
PARVATI	en	O
<3	rest	O
http://t.co/xMhhsKrpBV	en	O
#Hindus	rest	O
#Hinduism	rest	O
http://t.co/iNe3qJVdtL	en	O

Har	hi	O
Insaan	hi	O
ek	hi	O
Second	en	O
Chance	en	O
Deserve	en	O
karta	hi	O
hai	hi	O
.....	rest	O

RT	en	O
@BeingSalmanKhan	en	O
:	rest	O
Let's	en	O
cheer	en	O
for	en	O
Lalita	rest	B-PERSON
Babar	rest	I-PERSON
#RioOlympics2016	en	O
#MakeIndiaProud	en	O
https://t.co/lzOE2v3U7u	en	O

#Jaldoot	hi	O
3	rest	O
water	en	O
train	en	O
passing	en	O
Pandharpur	rest	B-PLACE
and	en	O
Kurduwadi	en	B-PLACE
enroute	en	O
to	en	O
#Latur	en	O
https://t.co/WThZC9gXvW	en	O

:	rest	O
LAST	en	O
NIGHT	en	O
MAHASHIVRATRI	rest	O
RUDRABHISHEK	rest	O
.....	rest	O
Abeer	hi	B-PERSON
Gulaal	hi	I-PERSON
sringaar	rest	B-PLACE
...	rest	O

@Ankit_Tyagi01	en	O
@ArvindKejriwal	en	O
@narendramodi	rest	O
sir	hi	O
Delhi	rest	B-PLACE
me	hi	O
Etne	hi	O
odd	en	O
even	en	O
ke	hi	O
poster	en	O
lage	hi	O
wo	hi	O
kab	hi	O
hatege	hi	O

pakistan	rest	B-PLACE
:	rest	O
-	rest	O
Haar	hi	O
jeet	hi	O
toh	hi	O
game	en	O
ka	hi	O
part	en	O
hai	hi	O
...	rest	O
Important	en	O
cheez	hi	O
yeh	hi	O
hai	hi	O
ki	hi	O
sabko	hi	O
batting	en	O
mili	hi	O
..!!	rest	O
#IndVsPak	rest	O
#CWC2015	rest	O
#BleedBlue	en	O

RT	en	O
@sailorsaurabh	hi	O
:	rest	O
Great	en	O
job	en	O
by	en	O
railway	en	B-ORGANISATION
ministry	en	I-ORGANISATION
.	rest	O
Mr.	rest	B-PERSON
Suresh	en	I-PERSON
Prabhu	hi	I-PERSON
setting	en	O
a	en	O
benchmark	en	O
of	en	O
custoner	en	O
service	en	O
for	en	O
other	en	O
ministries	en	O
....	rest	O
https	en	O
:/	rest	O

Sometimes	en	O
I	en	O
look	en	O
at	en	O
the	en	O
heavens	en	O
for	en	O
inspiration	en	O
..	rest	O
:)	rest	O
#Retrica	rest	O
#Sunshine	rest	O
http://t.co/1BR2RZGKbi	en	O

@raviishndtv	rest	O
or	hi	O
jor	hi	O
se	hi	O
chato	hi	O
Cong	en	B-ORGANISATION
ki	hi	O

RT	en	O
@ggiittiikkaa	hi	O
:	rest	O
Rahul	en	B-PERSON
Gandhi	rest	I-PERSON
:	rest	O
Hum	hi	O
chahte	hi	O
hain	hi	O
shirt	en	O
,	rest	O
chappal	hi	O
,	rest	O
kurte-pyjame	hi	O
ki	hi	O
sarkar	hi	O
chale	hi	O
Barkha	hi	O
:	rest	O
Epic	en	O
!	rest	O
Sagarika	hi	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
Brilliant	en	O
speech	en	O
!	rest	O
R	en	O

RT	en	O
@EconomicTimes	en	O
:	rest	O
.	rest	O
@ArvindKejriwal	en	O
should	en	O
make	en	O
public	en	O
apology	en	O
for	en	O
remarks	en	O
on	en	O
PM	rest	O
@narendramodi's	rest	O
degrees	en	O
:	rest	O
BJP	rest	B-ORGANISATION
https://t.co/8Nkm6lTV2M	en	O
https	en	O

RT	en	O
MLBANSAL	rest	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
RT	en	O
jsingh341	en	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
RT	en	O
ShatyUvma	en	O
:	rest	O
RT	en	O
cuteinsan	en	O
:	rest	O
Gurmeetramrahim	en	B-PERSON
#MSG100CroreClub	en	O
#MustWatchMSG	en	O
craze	en	O
for	en	O
MS	en	O
http://t.co/wfEmqNTcjS	en	O

PAPPU	en	B-PERSON
doing	en	O
chintan	en	O
in	en	O
Himalayas	en	B-PLACE
singing	en	O
"	rest	O
Mai	hi	O
aisa	hi	O
q	hi	O
hu	hi	O
,	rest	O
Mai	hi	O
aisa	hi	O
q	hi	O
hue	hi	O
"	rest	O
#RahulOnLeave	en	O
#RahulGandhi	rest	O
#WhereIsRahulGandhi	rest	O

RT	en	O
@calamur	rest	O
:	rest	O
"	rest	O
farce	en	O
masquerading	en	O
as	en	O
justice	en	O
"	rest	O
says	en	O
sandipan	rest	B-PERSON
Sharma	rest	I-PERSON
on	en	O
the	en	O
JNU	rest	B-ORGANISATION
suspensions	en	O
https://t.co/MDfhx7CmU8	en	O

Super	en	O
Model	en	O
Gizele	en	B-PERSON
Thakral's	en	I-PERSON
LEAKED	en	O
UNCENSORED	en	O
photoshoot	en	O
video	en	O
-	rest	O
1	rest	O
.	rest	O
(	rest	O
18+)	rest	O
See	en	O
the	en	O
full	en	O
video	en	O
at	en	O
:	rest	O
https://t.co/H9rrYYhdIZ	en	O
#gizelethakral	en	O

Can	en	O
You	en	O
Take	en	O
It	en	O
Ravish	rest	B-PERSON
Kumar	rest	I-PERSON
?	rest	O
:	rest	O
http://t.co/ZjDpAhxrgX	en	O
via	en	O
@youtube	en	O
#ndtv	en	O
#ravishkumar	rest	O

@aditi_tyagi	en	O
@praveenpandram	en	O
@LambaAlka	rest	O
@ZeeNews	en	O
aapne	hi	O
Saturday	en	O
ko	hi	O
gadi	hi	O
road	en	O
par	hi	O
nahi	hi	O
chalai	hi	O
,	rest	O
without	en	O
jam	hi	O
road	en	O
,	rest	O
90	rest	O
min	hi	O
Ka	hi	O
safar	hi	O
40	hi	O
min	hi	O
la	hi	O

Government	en	O
Should	en	O
Reconsider	en	O
Krishi	rest	O
Kalayan	hi	O
Cess	en	O
Imposition	en	O
:	rest	O
Assocham	rest	B-PERSON
:	rest	O
Government	en	O
should	en	O
reconsider	en	O
...	rest	O
https://t.co/BGQBPn9n1X	en	O
via	en	O
@ndtv	en	O

Yeh	hi	O
Jawaani	hi	O
Hai	hi	O
Deewani-Deepika	rest	B-PERSON
Padukone	rest	I-PERSON
,	rest	O
Ranbir	rest	B-PERSON
Kapoor	hi	I-PERSON
,	rest	O
Kalki	hi	B-PERSON
Koechlin	en	I-PERSON
,	rest	O
Aditya	en	B-PERSON
Roy	en	I-PERSON
Kapur	hi	I-PERSON
http://t.co/W0xrtVAJPz	en	O

@saurabhraajjain	hi	O
Shiv	hi	B-PERSON
Shankar	hi	I-PERSON
Kre	hi	O
apki	hi	O
hr	hi	O
murad	hi	O
puri	hi	O
yhi	hi	O
dua	hi	O
h	hi	O
hmri	hi	O
ap	hi	O
rhe	hi	O
sada	hi	O
khush	hi	O
yhi	hi	O
iltaza	hi	O
hmri	hi	O
.	rest	O
MahaShivratri	rest	O
ki	hi	O
apko	hi	O
hardik	hi	O
abhindn	rest	O
.	rest	O

@SrBachchan	hi	O
John	hi	B-PERSON
jani	hi	O
janardan	rest	O
...	rest	O
Tara	hi	O
rum	hi	O
pum	hi	O
pum	hi	O

#ChennaiFloods	rest	O
:	rest	O
IAF	rest	B-ORGANISATION
has	en	O
airlifted	en	O
17	en	O
teams	en	O
of	en	O
NDRF	en	B-ORGANISATION
teams	en	O
from	en	O
Delhi	rest	B-PLACE
,	rest	O
Bhubaneswar	hi	B-PLACE
,	rest	O
Bathinda	rest	B-PLACE
&	rest	O
2	rest	O
Columns	en	O
of	en	O
Army	en	O
.	rest	O
https://t.co/7peINeJesW	en	O

RT	en	O
@ChaitraSalian	rest	O
:	rest	O
Happy	en	O
MahaShivratri	rest	O
...	rest	O
Om	rest	O
namah	rest	O
Shiva	rest	B-PERSON

RT	en	O
@JustEditorials	en	O
:	rest	O
India	rest	B-PLACE
should	en	O
have	en	O
at	en	O
least	en	O
60	rest	O
Muslim	rest	O
MPs	rest	O
:	rest	O
Asaduddin	hi	B-PERSON
Owaisi	hi	I-PERSON
@EconomicTimes	en	O
http://t.co/Z1HqMoZG3L	en	O

@TimesNow	en	O
MC	en	O
press	en	O
conference	en	O
kya	hi	O
kr	hi	O
raha	hi	O
hai	hi	O
be	hi	O
,	rest	O
arrest	en	O
kr	hi	O
BC	rest	O
!	rest	O
Darpok	en	O
sahab	hi	O
sent	en	O
@GVLNRAO	en	O
to	en	O
press	en	O
conference	en	O
Where	en	O
z	en	O
re-signation	en	O
prasad	hi	B-PERSON

@binta_sweet	en	O
Aavu	rest	O
Naa	hi	O
kene	hi	O
yaaar	hi	O
It	en	O
hurts	en	O

Kya	hi	O
lifetime	en	O
like	en	O
hi	hi	O
karogi	hi	O
?	rest	O
Kabhi	hi	O
RT	en	O
nahi	hi	O
karogi	hi	O
?	rest	O

RT	en	O
@richaanirudh	rest	O
:	rest	O
Its	en	O
rare	en	O
tht	en	O
politicns	en	O
get	en	O
praised	en	O
by	en	O
#BigHeroes	en	O
.	rest	O
Was	en	O
happy	en	O
to	en	O
hear	en	O
how	en	O
@Saurabh_MLAgk	hi	O
helpd	en	O
Anandini	rest	B-PERSON
get	en	O
a	en	O
basketball	en	O
cou	en	O

#NihalBitla	rest	O
India's	rest	B-PLACE
face	en	O
of	en	O
Progeria	en	O
dies	en	O
in	en	O
Telangana	rest	B-PLACE
#RestInPeace	en	O
https://t.co/nQl1OPkpQ3	en	O
https://t.co/NIUkbtCVKi	en	O

@Sand_In_Deed	rest	O
:	rest	O
Ladkiya	hi	O
mujhe	hi	O
dekh	hi	O
ke	hi	O
pagal	hi	O
ho	hi	O
jati	hi	O
.	rest	O
Me-Kitni	hi	O
ladkiya	hi	O
pagal	hi	O
hui	hi	O
?	rest	O
He-Pic1	rest	O
Me-kaun	hi	O
kaun	hi	O
?	rest	O
He-Pic	rest	O
2	rest	O
&	rest	O
3	rest	O
https://t.co/ueR6DS3KpY	en	O

RT	en	O
@gautamverma23	en	O
:	rest	O
Virat	rest	B-PERSON
Kohli	rest	I-PERSON
should	en	O
play	en	O
till	en	O
his	en	O
50	rest	O
.	rest	O
Cos	en	O
he	en	O
has	en	O
no	en	O
career	en	O
as	en	O
a	en	O
commentator	en	O
.	rest	O
Cos	rest	O
"	rest	O
Bhenchod	hi	O
ne	hi	O
kya	hi	O
shot	hi	O
mara	hi	O
hai	hi	O
"	rest	O
is	en	O
not	en	O
a	en	O

RT	en	O
@AmitInsan12	rest	O
:	rest	O
@Gurmeetramrahim	en	O
#MSGmissionHumanity	en	O
Papa	en	O
ji	hi	O
watermelon	en	O
khao	hi	O
g	en	O
...	rest	O
aapke	hi	O
liye	hi	O
hai	hi	O
ji	hi	O
...	rest	O
https://t.co/IKFe257inD	en	O

MahaPrasaad	rest	O
On	en	O
Occasion	en	O
of	en	O
MahaShivRatri	en	O
by	en	O
Anaaval	hi	B-ORGANISATION
Shukaleshwar	hi	I-ORGANISATION
Mahadev	rest	I-ORGANISATION
Trust	en	I-ORGANISATION
.	rest	O
EveryBody	en	O
WelCome	en	O
!	rest	O
Oldest	en	O
SwayamBhu	hi	O
Ling	en	O
of	en	O
Bhagwaan	hi	O
Shankar	hi	B-PERSON
!	rest	O

@Nagendr_Sharma_	rest	O
Jai	hi	O
Shri	hi	O
Krishna	rest	B-PERSON
!	rest	O
Thank	en	O
u	en	O
!	rest	O
#MahaShivratri	rest	O
ki	hi	O
Shubha	hi	O
kamanaye	hi	O
!	rest	O
OmNamaShivaya	rest	O
http://t.co/abFHQ7KGjP	rest	O

@IALalika	rest	O
@Umarkarim89	rest	O
@ArifeenIbad	en	O
No	en	O
.	rest	O
Ballay	rest	O
Baaz	hi	O
kuch	hi	O
nhi	hi	O
karega	hi	O

Kon	hi	O
#Nhaye	hi	O
itni	hi	O
thnd	en	O
me	hi	O
3	rest	O
:)	rest	O

RT	en	O
@KyaUkhaadLega	hi	O
:	rest	O
When	en	O
a	en	O
non-marathi	en	O
girl	en	O
tried	en	O
to	hi	O
kiss	hi	O
Raj	hi	B-PERSON
Thackeray	en	I-PERSON
https://t.co/QVkkO3DROl	en	O

10lakh	rest	O
k	hi	O
suit	en	O
pe	hi	O
ek	hi	O
muffler	en	O
bhaari	hi	O
padh	hi	O
gya	hi	O
!!	rest	O
Dekhte	hi	O
hi	hi	O
dekhte	hi	O
sbko	hi	O
dhara	hi	O
shai	hi	O
kr	hi	O
gya	hi	O
!!	rest	O
#AAPSweep	rest	O
#DelhiDecides	en	O
#AAPStorm	rest	O

Gavran	en	O
chicken	en	O
&	rest	O
fish	en	O
fry	en	O
@	rest	O
Ghotawade	hi	B-PLACE
gaon	hi	I-PLACE
near	en	O
Hinjewadi	en	B-PLACE
phase3	en	I-PLACE
.	rest	O
@PuneFoodiez	en	O
https://t.co/ltExVWSJWx	en	O

